English
range:a-zA-Z

English incl. full-width chars
range:a-zA-Z

German
range:a-zA-ZäÄöÖüÜß

French
range:a-zA-Zéèàêâôçœ

Spanish
range:a-zA-Zñáéíóúü

Portuguese
range:a-zA-Zñáéíóúüôçãôê

Italian
range:a-zA-Zàèìòùéáóî

Norwegian
range:a-zA-ZæÆøØåÅéèêóòâô

Danish
range:a-zA-ZæÆøØåÅ

Swedish, Finnish
range:a-zA-ZåÅäÄöÖ

Russian
range:а-яА-ЯёЁeE

Ukrainian
range:а-яА-ЯґҐєЄіІїЇ

South Slavic
range:a-zA-Zа-шА-ШčČćĆđĐšŠžŽ

Romanian
range:a-zA-ZăĂâÂșȘțȚ

Greek
range:α-ωΑ-Ωó

Turkish
range:a-zA-ZçÇöÖüÜğĞıİşŞ

Polish
range:a-zA-ZąĄćĆęĘłŁńŃóÓśŚźŹżŻ

Czech && Slovak
range:a-zA-Zа-шА-ШčČćĆđĐšŠžŽ

Hungarian
range:a-zA-ZáÁéÉíÍóÓöÖúÚüÜ

Hebrew
range:א-ת

Arabic
range:ا-يآةىی

Vietnamese
range:a-yA-YăâđêôơưĂÂĐÊÔƠƯ

Thai
range:ก-๛

Chinese (simplified, GBK)
一乙画二十丁厂七卜人入八九几儿了力乃刀又三于干亏士工土才寸下大丈与万上小口巾山千乞川亿个勺久凡及夕丸么广亡门义之尸弓己已子卫也女飞刃习叉马乡四丰王井开夫天无元专云扎艺木五支厅不太犬区历尤友匹车巨牙屯比互切瓦止少日中冈贝内水见午牛手毛气升长仁什片仆化仇币仍仅斤爪反介父从今凶分乏公仓月氏勿欠风丹匀乌凤勾文六方火为斗忆订计户认心尺引丑巴孔队办以允予劝双书幻五玉刊示末未击打巧正扑扒功扔去甘世古节本术可丙左厉右石布龙平灭轧东卡北占业旧帅归且旦目叶甲申叮电号田由史只央兄叼叫另叨叹四生失禾丘付仗代仙们仪白仔他斥瓜乎丛令用甩印乐句匆册犯外处冬鸟务包饥主市立闪兰半汁汇头汉宁穴它讨写让礼训必议讯记永司尼民出辽奶奴加召皮边发孕圣对台矛纠母幼丝式刑动扛寺吉扣考托老执巩圾扩扫地扬场耳共芒亚芝朽朴机权过臣再协西压厌在有百存而页匠夸夺灰达列死成夹轨邪划迈毕至此贞师尘尖劣光当早吐吓虫曲团同吊吃因吸吗屿帆岁回岂刚则肉网年朱先丢舌竹迁乔伟传乒乓休伍伏优伐延件任伤价份华仰仿伙伪自血向似后行舟全会杀合兆企众爷伞创肌朵杂危旬旨负各名多争色壮冲冰庄庆亦刘齐交次衣产决充妄闭问闯羊并关米灯州汗污江池汤忙兴宇守宅字安讲军许论农讽设访寻那迅尽导异孙阵阳收阶阴防奸如妇好她妈戏羽观欢买红纤级约纪驰巡寿弄麦形进戒吞远违运扶抚坛技坏扰拒找批扯址走抄坝贡攻赤折抓扮抢孝均抛投坟抗坑坊抖护壳志扭块声把报却劫芽花芹芬苍芳严芦劳克苏杆杠杜材村杏极李杨求更束豆两丽医辰励否还歼来连步坚旱盯呈时吴助县里呆园旷围呀吨足邮男困吵串员听吩吹呜吧吼别岗帐财针钉告我乱利秃秀私每兵估体何但伸作伯伶佣低你住位伴身皂佛近彻役返余希坐谷妥含邻岔肝肚肠龟免狂犹角删条卵岛迎饭饮系言冻状亩况床库疗应冷这序辛弃冶忘闲间闷判灶灿弟汪沙汽沃泛沟没沈沉怀忧快完宋宏牢究穷灾良证启评补初社识诉诊词译君灵即层尿尾迟局改张忌际陆阿陈阻附妙妖妨努忍劲鸡驱纯纱纳纲驳纵纷纸纹纺驴纽奉玩环武青责现表规抹拢拔拣担坦押抽拐拖拍者顶拆拥抵拘势抱垃拉拦拌幸招坡披拨择抬其取苦若茂苹苗英范直茄茎茅林枝杯柜析板松枪构杰述枕丧或卧事刺枣雨卖矿码厕奔奇奋态欧垄妻轰顷转斩轮软到非叔肯齿些虎虏肾贤尚旺具果味昆国昌畅明易昂典固忠咐呼鸣咏呢岸岩帖罗帜岭凯败贩购图钓制知垂牧物乖刮秆和季委佳侍供使例版侄侦侧凭侨佩货依的迫质欣征往爬彼径所舍金命斧爸采受乳贪念贫肤肺肢肿胀朋股肥服胁周昏鱼兔狐忽狗备饰饱饲变京享店夜庙府底剂郊废净盲放刻育闸闹郑券卷单炒炊炕炎炉沫浅法泄河沾泪油泊沿泡注泻泳泥沸波泼泽治怖性怕怜怪学宝宗定宜审宙官空帘实试郎诗肩房诚衬衫视话诞询该详建肃录隶居届刷屈弦承孟孤陕降限妹姑姐姓始驾参艰线练组细驶织终驻驼绍经贯奏春帮珍玻毒型挂封持项垮挎城挠政赴赵挡挺括拴拾挑指垫挣挤拼挖按挥挪某甚革荐巷带草茧茶荒茫荡荣故胡南药标枯柄栋相查柏柳柱柿栏树要咸威歪研砖厘厚砌砍面耐耍牵残殃轻鸦皆背战点临览竖省削尝是盼眨哄显哑冒映星昨畏趴胃贵界虹虾蚁思蚂虽品咽骂哗咱响哈咬咳哪炭峡罚贱贴骨钞钟钢钥钩卸缸拜看矩怎牲选适秒香种秋科重复竿段便俩贷顺修保促侮俭俗俘信皇泉鬼侵追俊盾待律很须叙剑逃食盆胆胜胞胖脉勉狭狮独狡狱狠贸怨急饶蚀饺饼弯将奖哀亭亮度迹庭疮疯疫疤姿亲音帝施闻阀阁差养美姜叛送类迷前首逆总炼炸炮烂剃洁洪洒浇浊洞测洗活派洽染济洋洲浑浓津恒恢恰恼恨举觉宣室宫宪突穿窃客冠语扁袄祖神祝误诱说诵垦退既屋昼费陡眉孩除险院娃姥姨姻娇怒架贺盈勇怠柔垒绑绒结绕骄绘给络骆绝绞统耕耗艳泰珠班素蚕顽盏匪捞栽捕振载赶起盐捎捏埋捉捆捐损都哲逝捡换挽热恐壶挨耻耽恭莲莫荷获晋恶真框桂档桐株桥桃格校核样根索哥速逗栗配翅辱唇夏础破原套逐烈殊顾轿较顿毙致柴桌虑监紧党晒眠晓鸭晃晌晕蚊哨哭恩唤啊唉罢峰圆贼贿钱钳钻铁铃铅缺氧特牺造乘敌秤租积秧秩称秘透笔笑笋债借值倚倾倒倘俱倡候俯倍倦健臭射躬息徒徐舰舱般航途拿爹爱颂翁脆脂胸胳脏胶脑狸狼逢留皱饿恋桨浆衰高席准座脊症病疾疼疲效离唐资凉站剖竞部旁旅畜阅羞瓶拳粉料益兼烤烘烦烧烛烟递涛浙涝酒涉消浩海涂浴浮流润浪浸涨烫涌悟悄悔悦害宽家宵宴宾窄容宰案请朗诸读扇袜袖袍被祥课谁调冤谅谈谊剥恳展剧屑弱陵陶陷陪娱娘通能难预桑绢绣验继球理捧堵描域掩捷排掉堆推掀授教掏掠培接控探据掘职基著勒黄萌萝菌菜萄菊萍菠营械梦梢梅检梳梯桶救副票戚爽聋袭盛雪辅辆虚雀堂常匙晨睁眯眼悬野啦晚啄距跃略蛇累唱患唯崖崭崇圈铜铲银甜梨犁移笨笼笛符第敏做袋悠偿偶偷您售停偏假得衔盘船斜盒鸽悉欲彩领脚脖脸脱象够猜猪猎猫猛馅馆凑减毫麻痒痕廊康庸鹿盗章竟商族旋望率着盖粘粗粒断剪兽清添淋淹渠渐混渔淘液淡深婆梁渗情惜惭悼惧惕惊惨惯寇寄宿窑密谋谎祸谜逮敢屠弹随蛋隆隐婚婶颈绩绪续骑绳维绵绸绿琴斑替款堪搭塔越趁趋超提堤博揭喜插揪搜煮援裁搁搂搅握揉斯期欺联散惹葬葛董葡敬葱落朝辜葵棒棋植森椅椒棵棍棉棚棕惠惑逼厨厦硬确雁殖裂雄暂雅辈悲紫辉敞赏掌晴暑最量喷晶喇遇喊景践跌跑遗蛙蛛蜓喝喂喘喉幅帽赌赔黑铸铺链销锁锄锅锈锋锐短智毯鹅剩稍程稀税筐等筑策筛筒答筋筝傲傅牌堡集焦傍储奥街惩御循艇舒番释禽腊脾腔鲁猾猴然馋装蛮就痛童阔善羡普粪尊道曾焰港湖渣湿温渴滑湾渡游滋溉愤慌惰愧愉慨割寒富窜窝窗遍裕裤裙谢谣谦属屡强粥疏隔隙絮嫂登缎缓编骗缘瑞魂肆摄摸填搏塌鼓摆携搬摇搞塘摊蒜勤鹊蓝墓幕蓬蓄蒙蒸献禁楚想槐榆楼概赖酬感碍碑碎碰碗碌雷零雾雹输督龄鉴睛睡睬鄙愚暖盟歇暗照跨跳跪路跟遣蛾蜂嗓置罪罩错锡锣锤锦键锯矮辞稠愁筹签简毁舅鼠催傻像躲微愈遥腰腥腹腾腿触解酱痰廉新韵意粮数煎塑慈煤煌满漠源滤滥滔溪溜滚滨粱滩慎誉塞谨福群殿辟障嫌嫁叠缝缠四静碧璃墙撇嘉摧截誓境摘摔聚蔽慕暮蔑模榴榜榨歌遭酷酿酸磁愿需弊裳颗嗽蜻蜡蝇蜘赚锹锻舞稳算箩管僚鼻魄貌膜膊膀鲜疑馒裹敲豪膏遮腐瘦辣竭端旗精歉熄熔漆漂漫滴演漏慢寨赛察蜜谱嫩翠熊凳骡缩五慧撕撒趣趟撑播撞撤增聪鞋蕉蔬横槽樱橡飘醋醉震霉瞒题暴瞎影踢踏踩踪蝶蝴嘱墨镇靠稻黎稿稼箱箭篇僵躺僻德艘膝膛熟摩颜毅糊遵潜潮懂额慰劈操燕薯薪薄颠橘整融醒餐嘴蹄器赠默镜赞篮邀衡膨雕磨凝辨辩糖糕燃澡激懒壁避缴戴擦鞠藏霜霞瞧蹈螺穗繁辫赢糟糠燥臂翼骤鞭覆蹦镰翻鹰警攀蹲颤瓣爆疆壤耀躁嚼嚷籍魔灌蠢霸露囊罐匕刁四丐歹戈夭仑讥冗邓五艾夯凸卢叭叽皿凹囚矢乍尔冯玄邦迂邢芋芍吏夷吁吕吆屹廷迄臼仲伦伊肋旭匈凫妆亥汛讳讶讹讼诀弛阱驮驯纫玖玛韧抠扼汞扳抡坎坞抑拟抒芙芜苇芥芯芭杖杉巫杈甫匣轩卤肖吱吠呕呐吟呛吻吭邑囤吮岖牡佑佃伺囱肛肘甸狈鸠彤灸刨庇吝庐闰兑灼沐沛汰沥沦汹沧沪忱诅诈罕屁坠妓姊妒纬玫卦坷坯拓坪坤拄拧拂拙拇拗茉昔苛苫苟苞茁苔枉枢枚枫杭郁矾奈奄殴歧卓昙哎咕呵咙呻咒咆咖帕账贬贮氛秉岳侠侥侣侈卑刽刹肴觅忿瓮肮肪狞庞疟疙疚卒氓炬沽沮泣泞泌沼怔怯宠宛衩祈诡帚屉弧弥陋陌函姆虱叁绅驹绊绎契贰玷玲珊拭拷拱挟垢垛拯荆茸茬荚茵茴荞荠荤荧荔栈柑栅柠枷勃柬砂泵砚鸥轴韭虐昧盹咧昵昭盅勋哆咪哟幽钙钝钠钦钧钮毡氢秕俏俄俐侯徊衍胚胧胎狰饵峦奕咨飒闺闽籽娄烁炫洼柒涎洛恃恍恬恤宦诫诬祠诲屏屎逊陨姚娜蚤骇耘耙秦匿埂捂捍袁捌挫挚捣捅埃耿聂荸莽莱莉莹莺梆栖桦栓桅桩贾酌砸砰砾殉逞哮唠哺剔蚌蚜畔蚣蚪蚓哩圃鸯唁哼唆峭唧峻赂赃钾铆氨秫笆俺赁倔殷耸舀豺豹颁胯胰脐脓逛卿鸵鸳馁凌凄衷郭斋疹紊瓷羔烙浦涡涣涤涧涕涩悍悯窍诺诽袒谆祟恕娩骏琐麸琉琅措捺捶赦埠捻掐掂掖掷掸掺勘聊娶菱菲萎菩萤乾萧萨菇彬梗梧梭曹酝酗厢硅硕奢盔匾颅彪眶晤曼晦冕啡畦趾啃蛆蚯蛉蛀唬啰唾啤啥啸崎逻崔崩婴赊铐铛铝铡铣铭矫秸秽笙笤偎傀躯兜衅徘徙舶舷舵敛翎脯逸凰猖祭烹庶庵痊阎阐眷焊焕鸿涯淑淌淮淆渊淫淳淤淀涮涵惦悴惋寂窒谍谐裆袱祷谒谓谚尉堕隅婉颇绰绷综绽缀巢琳琢琼揍堰揩揽揖彭揣搀搓壹搔葫募蒋蒂韩棱椰焚椎棺榔椭粟棘酣酥硝硫颊雳翘凿棠晰鼎喳遏晾畴跋跛蛔蜒蛤鹃喻啼喧嵌赋赎赐锉锌甥掰氮氯黍筏牍粤逾腌腋腕猩猬惫敦痘痢痪竣翔奠遂焙滞湘渤渺溃溅湃愕惶寓窖窘雇谤犀隘媒媚婿缅缆缔缕骚瑟鹉瑰搪聘斟靴靶蓖蒿蒲蓉楔椿楷榄楞楣酪碘硼碉辐辑频睹睦瞄嗜嗦暇畸跷跺蜈蜗蜕蛹嗅嗡嗤署蜀幌锚锥锨锭锰稚颓筷魁衙腻腮腺鹏肄猿颖煞雏馍馏禀痹廓痴靖誊漓溢溯溶滓溺寞窥窟寝褂裸谬媳嫉缚缤剿四赘熬赫蔫摹蔓蔗蔼熙蔚兢榛榕酵碟碴碱碳辕辖雌墅嘁踊蝉嘀幔镀舔熏箍箕箫舆僧孵瘩瘟彰粹漱漩漾慷寡寥谭褐褪隧嫡缨五撵撩撮撬擒墩撰鞍蕊蕴樊樟橄敷豌醇磕磅碾憋嘶嘲嘹蝠蝎蝌蝗蝙嘿幢镊镐稽篓膘鲤鲫褒瘪瘤瘫凛澎潭潦澳潘澈澜澄憔懊憎翩褥谴鹤憨履嬉豫缭撼擂擅蕾薛薇擎翰噩橱橙瓢蟥霍霎辙冀踱蹂蟆螃螟噪鹦黔穆篡篷篙篱儒膳鲸瘾瘸糙燎濒憾懈窿缰壕藐檬檐檩檀礁磷瞭瞬瞳瞪曙蹋蟋蟀嚎赡镣魏簇儡徽爵朦臊鳄糜癌懦豁臀藕藤瞻嚣鳍癞瀑襟璧戳攒孽蘑藻鳖蹭蹬簸簿蟹靡癣羹鬓攘蠕巍鳞糯譬霹躏髓蘸镶瓤四矗廣香豐公長華吳為貿發

Chinese (traditional)
的是不我一有大在人了中到資要可以這個你會好為上來就學交也用能如文時沒說他看提那問生過下請天們所多麼小想得之還電出工對都機自後子而訊站去心只家知國台很信成章何同道地發法無然但嗎當於本現年前真最和新因果定意情點題其事方清科樣些吧三此位理行作經者什謝名日正華話開實再城愛與二動比高面又車力或種像應女教分手打已次長太明己路起相主關鳳間呢覺該十外凰友才民系進使她著各少全兩回加將感第性球式把被老公龍程論及別給聽水重體做校裡常東風您灣啦見解等部原月美先管區錯音否啊找網樂讓通入期選較四場由書它快從歡數表怎至立內合目望認幾社告更版度考喜頭難光買今身許弟若算記代統處完號接言政玩師字並男計誰山張黨每且結改非星連哈建放直轉報活設變指氣研陳試西五希取神化物王戰近世受義反單死任跟便空林士臺卻北隊功必聲寫平影業金檔片討色容央妳向市則員興利強白價安呵特思叫總辦保花議傳元求份件持萬未究決投哪喔笑貓組獨級走支曾標流竹兄阿室卡馬共需海口門般線語命觀視朋聯參格黃錢修失兒住八腦板吃另換即象料錄拿專遠速基幫形確候裝孩備歌界除南器畫訴差講類英案帶久乎掉迷量引整似耶奇制邊型超識雖怪飛始品運賽費夢故班權破驗眼滿念造軍精務留服六圖收舍半讀願李底約雄課答令深票達演早賣棒夠黑院假曲火準百談勝碟術推存治離易往況晚示證段導傷調團七永剛哥甚德殺怕包列概照夜排客絕軟商根九切條集千落竟越待忘盡據雙供稱座值消產紅跑嘛園附硬雲遊展執聞唱育斯某技唉息苦質油救效須介首助職例熱畢節害擊亂態嗯寶倒注停古輸規福親查復步舉魚斷終輕環練印隨依趣限響省局續司角簡極幹篇羅佛克陽武疑送拉習源免志鳥煩足館仍低廣土呀樓壞兵顯率聖碼眾爭初誤楚責境野預具智壓係青貴順負魔適哇測慢懷懂史配嗚味亦醫迎舞戀細灌甲帝句屬靈評騎宜敗左追狂敢春狗際遇族群痛右康佳楊木病戲項抓徵善官護博補石爾營歷隻按妹里編歲擇溫守血領尋田養謂居異雨止跳君爛優封拜惡啥浪核聊急狀陸激模攻忙良劇牛壘增維靜陣抱勢嚴詞亞夫簽悲密幕毒廠爽緣店吳蘭睡致江宿翻香蠻警控趙冷威微坐週宗普登母絡午恐套巴雜創舊輯幸劍亮述堂酒麗牌仔腳突搞父俊暴防吉禮素招草周房餐慮充府背典仁漫景紹諸琴憶援尤缺扁罵純惜授皮松委湖誠麻置靠繼判益波姐既射欲刻堆釋含承退莫劉昨旁紀趕製尚藝肉律鐵奏樹毛罪筆彩註歸彈虎衛刀皆鍵售塊險榮播施銘囉漢賞欣升葉螢載嘿弄鐘付寄鬼哦燈呆洋嘻布磁薦檢派構媽藍貼豬策紙暗巧努雷架享宣逢均擔啟濟罷呼劃偉島歉郭訓穿詳沙督梅顧敵協輪略慧幻臉短鷹衝朝忍游河批混窗鄉蛋季散冊棄熟獎唯藏婚鏡緊猜喝尊乾縣伯偏偷秋層顆食淡申冠衣僅帳贊購犯敬勇洲束鬥徒嘉柔績笨擁漂獅詩圍乖孤姓吸私避範抗蓋祝序曉富譯巨秀餘輝插察慶積愈端移宮揮爆港雪碩借帥丟括掛盤偶末廳朱凡驚貨滅醒虛瑞拍遺忠誌透烈銀頂雅諾圓熊替休材挑俠雞累互掌唸米伴輔降豪籃洗健飯憐瘋宏困址兮操臨騙咧藥綠尼蔡玉辛輩敏減彼街聚郎泡恨蘇縮樞碰採默婆股童符抽獲宇廢贏肯砍鋼歐屆禁蒼脫漸仙淚觸途財箱厭籍冰濤訂哭穩析傑堅橋懶賢絲露森危佔茶慣塵佈爸階夏誼瓶哩慘械隱豐旅椰亡汽貝娘寒遭吹暑珍零刊郵村乃予賴搖納煙倫尾狼浮骨杯隔洪織詢振忽索惠峰席喵胡租款擾企刺芳鼠折頻冒癡陰哲針伊寂嘴倚霸揚沉悔蟲菜距複鼓摩鄭莊副頁燒弱暫剩豆探耐祖遍蕭握愁龜哀髮延庫隆盟傻眉固秘卷搭昭寧託辯覆吵耳閒撥沈昇胖丁妙殘違稍媒憂銷恩顏船奈映井拼屋乘京藉洞川憲擬寢塞倍戶擺桌域勞賺皇逃鴻橫牙拖齊農滾障搬奶烏瞭鬆戴譜酷棋嚇摸額瓜役怨染迫醉鎖震床鬧佩牠徐尺干潮帽盛孫屁淨凱撞迴損伙牽厲惑羊冬桃艦眠伍溪飄泰宋圈競閃縱崇滑乙俗淺蓮紫溝旋攝聰毀庭麥描妨勒儀陪榜闆慕耀獻審蟹巷諒姊逐踏岸葛臥洽寞邦藤拳阻蠍麵殊憑拒池邪航驅裁翔填奧函鎮丌寬頗槍遙穹啪閱鋒砂恭塔賀魂睛逸旗薩丸厚齋芬革庸舒飲閉勵頓仰閣孟昌訪緒裕勿州闡搶掃糊宙嘗菩賜赤喊盜擎勸奮慈儘污狐罰幽准兼尖彰灰番衡鮮擴毫誇砲拆監欄遲証傾鬱汪紛托漏渡姑秒吾窩輛齡跌浩肥獸煞抹酸稅陷谷沖杜胸甘胞誕豈辭牆涼碎晶邱邏脆噴玫娃培咱潛祥築孔柏叭邀猶妻估荒袋徑垃傲淑圾旦億截幣羽婦泥欺弦籌捨忌串伸喇恥繁廖逛勁臭魯壯捕窮拔于醜莉糟炸坡蒙腿坦怒甜韓緩悉扯割艾胎恆玲朵泉湯猛駕幼坪巫彎膽昏鞋怡吐唐悠盾躍侵丹鑑澤薪逝彥后召呂碧晨辨植痴瑰釣軒勤珠濃悟磨剪逼玄暖躲洛症擋敝礙亨遜蜜盼姆賦彬壁繳捷乏戒憾滴桑菲嫌愉爬惱刪嘆抵棚摘蔣箭夕翁牲蹟勉萊潔貪恰曰僑滄咖唷扣采奔泳跡涯奪抄療署誓盃騷翼屠咪霧涉鍾踢謀犧焦涵礎繞俱霹壢唬氏徹吝曼壽粉廉炎禍耗炮啡肚貢鼻挖貌捐融筋云穌撿飽鈴靂鳴奉燃飾繪黎捲恢瞧茫幅迪柳瑜矛吊侯瑪撐薄敦擠墨琪凌側楓嗨梯梁廷儒咬嵐覽兔怖稿齒獄爺邁悶喬姿蹤賓傢弘韻嶺咦褲殼孝仇譽妮懼促駛疼兇粗耍糕仲裂吟陀賭爵哉虧鍋刷旭晴蝶闊洩頑牧契轟羞拾錦逆墮夾枝瓦舟悅惹疏銳翹哎綜綱扇駐屏堪彌貫愚抬喂靖狠餅凝鄰擦滋坤蛙災莎毅卒汝征贈斗拋秦辱塗披允偵慾夥朗笛劫魅欽慰荷挺矣迅禪遷鹿秤彭肩讚丙鵝痕液漲巡烤賤丈趨沿濫措么扭捉碗爐髒叔祕腰漠翅余膠妥謠缸芒陵雯軌蝦寸呦灑貞蜂鑽廁鶴摔盒虫氛悄霖愧斜屍循倆堡旺噁叉燕津臣喪茂椅纏刑脈杉泊撒遞疲桿趁欠盈晃蛇牡慎粒繫倦溜遵腐疾鴨璃牢劣患祂呈渾劑妖玻塑飆伏弊扮儂渴歪苗汗陶棟琳蓉埋叡澎併泣騰柯催暢勾櫻阮斥搜踩返壇垂喚儲販匆添坑柴鄧糖昆暮櫃娟腹煮泛稀茲抑攜芭框彷罐虹拷萍臂襲敘吻仿賊羯浴体翠燦敲脅侶蟻秩佑謹寡岳賠掩匙曹紐籤晉喻綿詠攤馨珊孕杰拘喲羨膚肝袍罩叛禦謎嫁廟腸謊潘埔卜占攔煌俄札驟陌澄倉匪宵鈕崗盪卸旨粽貿舌曆叮咒鑰蘋祭屈陋雀睹媚娜誘衷菁殿撕蠢惟囂踴跨膀筒紋乳仗軸撤潭彿桂憤捧袖埃壹赫謙匯魏粹傅寮猴衰辜懇桶吋衫瞬凍獵瓊卿戚卓殖潑譬翰刮斌枉樑龐閩宅麟宰梭糾叢雕澳斃穎腔佇躺划寺鍊胃昂勳驕卑螞墓冥妄董淋盧償姻砸踐殷潤銅盲扎駁濕湊炒尿穴蟑拓詭謬淫蕩鼎斬堯偽餓馳蚊瘟肢挫槽扶兆僧昧螂匹芝奸聘眷熙猩癢帖貧賄撲籠丘顛訝瑋尹詗柱袁漆毋辣棍矩佐澡淵痞矮戈勃吞肆抖咳亭淘穗黏岡歧屑攏瀟諧遣診祈霜熬饒闖婉緻雁覓諷膜掙斤帆鋪淒瑟艇壺苑懸詹詮濾掰稚辰募懿慨哼汁佬纖肅遨漁恕蝴墊昱竿縫蹈鞭僕豫岩輻歹甄斑淹崎駿薰婷寵棵弓犬涂剎郁坎煎螺遮枯颱昔癮蒂墜唔瞎箏唇錶籲冤禱甩傘醬范焉嬌駝淪碳沾撫溶疊几蠟湧氧絃娛皓奴頹嘎趟揭噹剝墾狹魁坊鹽屎郝珮摧栗菊瘦鈞匿磚噓縛嘟盆債霞挽逍畔蘊頸穫畏餵脾姬赴囊噪熄錫訣肇璋暈濁伐峽竊枕倘慌垮帕瑩琦廂渺臟削鑼虐豔薇霉衍臘喧娶遂睜裙韋矢伺釘嬰蓄姦廿堵葬蓬鴉嚐挨蕾璿摯券廚醇呻霍剃漿葡暨濱履撈咕耕棉爍尉艱妓棺鵬蒸癌緯菌撇懲綁甫崩魄拂汰氓歇蘿嘸萄蕃曝疋嚮胏燭膩襄妝髓樸薯頌薛灘橘貳嘲歎枚侮豹巢酬碑翩蠶遼礦屢譴卵撰攀肌馮宴盞阪浦迦頒煉尬脹闢艘株祇湘飼爹梨嘍侍疫鵰黯并鋁弗爪鄙釵栽狸諮柄悸喉擅劈秉芷裸鏘賈逗寓咚璞燙鉛嘯炳嶼豎惶仕挪柵迄頃窄鷗鰱郊倩兜繭磊抒夷綽溯拙僚芙杖潰凶鴿妒沌祺吶卦聆棲蠅佮唾彙楣匠蛛悼舜耿瞄芋瞞竭茵吼苛浸拯剋荳沛掠廊凸攪俺酌倡朦蕉暱煥掏蟬燄狄繩惰芽裹宛御贖燥滔貶悍袂墳頡啤押尷顫鈍腥締糧啞檳簿斧腫綸僵齣轄蹲敷喘紮釀祐肖癒隧嗜檬逕碌襟凋圭寇汙哨倪筠樺詐姜旬禿脂噢撼釁庚炫譚慚澀崔貸鬍曬琉捏綺膝拭闇醋膨槓鑫瀑喃剖襪逾涅扳惘凳呃掘捍榔竅蝸曠梵暇稻檸抉輾蔚鉤蔔鶯匡蜘禎嗶窟亟諦溢黛晦伶逮傍蔥刁堤恍匣諜禧轎聳瀚斐忿泓拐驢罕沫綻刃窈渝仄瑛葵嚕繡奕窺瀏隸蔽仟斂丞詰鱉疤膏錐窕皺晰暉舅孰煽姚鈔袱絆焚蘆鹹沮嘔瞪淳丐茹槃菱篠涕襯蝕溉瑄翟怠鈺軀肺擲丑奢蔭靶紗芸佰峻阱哄腎庄囡闌戳腕菸凹蟾蒐呱巾雛螃盯饋壟毓犀逞姨穆樵閥瀰蹺擱隙疵憧懺琨闕萱悵輒搏榕飢搗渣眺虞俯紳謗瓏咫俏淆蜀楠乞詛勻貂寰迋敞跪囚溺駱憬葦脊瑤疆乍杆眸竄孽卅夭簧徘饅趴鎚啼冗緝絮啄沸萃嘶鴛禽憊徨屐輿邂掀嫖苟檯矯鐸稜嘩徊拱蕙徬滯吠妞氾芹叩朽儕赦汐丰虔茅棠崙膳魎儡鴦懦滲邵筱畜崖瑕蕊揣擒挂屯莽矽侏弧澈餃奎裘塌餌偎瀉蔓彗樽銜茍磋萎廓憫鑄莖殲壤澆蚤恃瞻拚汀椒嚼粥磅佫勘脖噸瀾鍛笙厄嚷伽徽隅寥繽簾烘茜馴噎廈閏煤鏈鏽誡頰俐曳蓓曖郤淌喀崑蔑峙躁菇逅雇毆泌酥繕莓轅駭巍糗扛杏茁琵礁穢岔僻焊嗡誦瞌捌遁贓渦琮卯鋸扔甦鄒蒞隘蹋湛晝岫蟄樁藐汲祿皂瀨絨耽糞粵滷曜懋咎痘聶垢瞳閔睿跤鑒躬斟淇莒毯倖騁岱廬殃橄恤嘰鱗濛芥欖楷硫苔麒椎禹喙釐裊亥倌吭訶裔梓驀巖幟瓣狡惕矇怯嫩龔嚎豚埠暸唆妃瓢蹄廝譏啃琶愿噱狷搪氫橙咆靡砌筷兌溼呸鍍踹塚祟懈朮搓攸橡膛俞祉冀炊瓷遐攬鷺茄蜢塘郡韜挾牟糙閻旻贅霆呎炭霄媳瘤猿颺煚鎧蝠鉅苓傀燼墅璇睏愣恬嫉瑣嫂淼梳憎摟藻酵屜陡摺簫饗桐蚱曦璧偈蹦昶嚨錚嗤戌屌耘裳啾嶸胺篤烹鞏厝疚鷥洶薔沐咽烙畸諱揍曙銬朔涓睬磯岐悽鯽楞鯉荊偕徜饑骯藹轍恁霈誅鞠茉煜傭嗓酹曇銓艷繃峨揉珈鵑誨臆焰雋熔堇韌扒憨舵肛戊壩摳骷碘鞍冕榨肘羔哺霓巳鏟蚵惆駒擷稽羹紡蛻趾弔豁褪癸眨臻慷蝙朧沼艙柚抨葭枷靨硝絢絞纜訕褚硨嫣蒲丫鸚蒹憩懊聾盎婊盔巒矜凜舖鵡蜴惚疇羈媛塹汎瘡韶憋祁詬搔蜥袒奄忱玖拌悴祠扼髏筑蛤茱騏捶鬚亢葔艸篩嶽糢慵戮跎砰侖煒籬笈癱吏痊庶厥棘娑沁窘鯨縷鹼儼棧蔬鳩閑迢恣昀泠漣眩噫娥荼鱷鏢侃虜俾樟榴嚀炬竇笠翱莘躇翡薑梟匕藩徉觴揀吱皈墉傌梢巔躊萌幌杭僥欒奠痲夸瘖芯蟀驛耨禾瑾塾儉沱腺櫥殭惋擻噗嗆抴蛀渲酋跆埸嬉愴噶耙憔撓羲扑眶蠣蹉孵澱慟灸愕淤狙檻嗈霎嗽兢瑚冉甸怔蠹綴諂灼紊彤荐詣眛稟餾蒜窯訐机炯頤繆扉嵩緬朕蟋瀕剔侷釷肋噩佢揖圳蕪褻嶄踅蜻塢綾冶惦梧罣殆兀訟臼踮炙雌嘖褒竺匈葳旱骰閹甭訢霏酪雍飪勛煦漓嫻揪囝嬋佼玟葷俘癖瞋咄幢迂蓊疹儸桔訛籐瞇猖泄鑿咻晏誣漪辮藺癥妾琇蜓烽舔娣汶詔侈膺渚槌鞘噬咐璀肪羚羿葫箔庇儷囑顱璽褐擂遑縈罹粘慄釗彪瘀蛾餒洹諭胚卉拇熾睦鯊碴辟漱窒惺譎勦迺臀瘓褔渠弋咸貍吽痔靄軾姥璁鈣漾跛翎磷噯吩敕氮鮑俟婿尪諺愷裴汞剿瞥氯槳仝瀛骸鉗鎔靚漩攘垣荻咯簣茗桓滸椏珀痠靴咀穀矗瘴璟籽晒瀝弩洸婪翊揹俑磕暐撩崢鵲昕寐徙遴濯堉跋隕丕簇鸝筍鬢竑繹鎳闋燿胥蚓嗔嬴榷尸蜍夙睞蚯謾璜湄鰻棕箋垚蠱訥鴕痺殉墟旄檀竣熹沂峭葾拈隍韃嗅佯蚣躪僱乩麓酗寅洒媲矚鋇誹拗朴罔螳撮睽漬摹捫搧蹂媄紓蔗曄隼憚睭箍奚擄咿瀆霾叨邃稠淮驍咩岑聿吮銃癲敖蜈鈑滂酉芻

Japanese
ぁあぃいぅうぇえぉおかがきぎくぐけげこごさざしじすずせぜそぞただちぢっつづてでとどなにぬねのはばぱひびぴふぶぷへべぺほぼぽまみむめもゃやゅゆょよらりるれろゎわゐゑをんァアィイゥウェエォオカガキギクグケゲコゴサザシジスズセゼソゾタダチヂッツヅテデトドナニヌネノハバパヒビピフブプヘベペホボポマミムメモャヤュユョヨラリルレロヮワヰヱヲンヴヵヶａｂｃｄｅｆｇｈｉｊｋｌｍｎｏｐｑｒｓｔｕｖｗｘｙｚＡＢＣＤＥＦＧＨＩＪＫＬＭＮＯＰＱＲＳＴＵＶＷＸＹＺ０１２３４５６７８９①②③④⑤⑥⑦⑧⑨⑩⑪⑫⑬⑭⑮⑯⑰⑱⑲⑳ⅠⅡⅢⅣⅤⅥⅦⅧⅨⅩ㍉㌔㌢㍍㌘㌧㌃㌶㍑㍗㌍㌦㌣㌫㍊㌻㎜㎝㎞㎎㎏㏄㎡㍻〝〟№㏍℡㊤㊥㊦㊧㊨㈱㈲㈹㍾㍽㍼亜唖娃阿哀愛挨姶逢葵茜穐悪握渥旭葦芦鯵梓圧斡扱宛姐虻飴絢綾鮎或粟袷安庵按暗案闇鞍杏以伊位依偉囲夷委威尉惟意慰易椅為畏異移維緯胃萎衣謂違遺医井亥域育郁磯一壱溢逸稲茨芋鰯允印咽員因姻引飲淫胤蔭院陰隠韻吋右宇烏羽迂雨卯鵜窺丑碓臼渦嘘唄欝蔚鰻姥厩浦瓜閏噂云運雲荏餌叡営嬰影映曳栄永泳洩瑛盈穎頴英衛詠鋭液疫益駅悦謁越閲榎厭円園堰奄宴延怨掩援沿演炎焔煙燕猿縁艶苑薗遠鉛鴛塩於汚甥凹央奥往応押旺横欧殴王翁襖鴬鴎黄岡沖荻億屋憶臆桶牡乙俺卸恩温穏音下化仮何伽価佳加可嘉夏嫁家寡科暇果架歌河火珂禍禾稼箇花苛茄荷華菓蝦課嘩貨迦過霞蚊俄峨我牙画臥芽蛾賀雅餓駕介会解回塊壊廻快怪悔恢懐戒拐改魁晦械海灰界皆絵芥蟹開階貝凱劾外咳害崖慨概涯碍蓋街該鎧骸浬馨蛙垣柿蛎鈎劃嚇各廓拡撹格核殻獲確穫覚角赫較郭閣隔革学岳楽額顎掛笠樫橿梶鰍潟割喝恰括活渇滑葛褐轄且鰹叶椛樺鞄株兜竃蒲釜鎌噛鴨栢茅萱粥刈苅瓦乾侃冠寒刊勘勧巻喚堪姦完官寛干幹患感慣憾換敢柑桓棺款歓汗漢澗潅環甘監看竿管簡緩缶翰肝艦莞観諌貫還鑑間閑関陥韓館舘丸含岸巌玩癌眼岩翫贋雁頑顔願企伎危喜器基奇嬉寄岐希幾忌揮机旗既期棋棄機帰毅気汽畿祈季稀紀徽規記貴起軌輝飢騎鬼亀偽儀妓宜戯技擬欺犠疑祇義蟻誼議掬菊鞠吉吃喫桔橘詰砧杵黍却客脚虐逆丘久仇休及吸宮弓急救朽求汲泣灸球究窮笈級糾給旧牛去居巨拒拠挙渠虚許距鋸漁禦魚亨享京供侠僑兇競共凶協匡卿叫喬境峡強彊怯恐恭挟教橋況狂狭矯胸脅興蕎郷鏡響饗驚仰凝尭暁業局曲極玉桐粁僅勤均巾錦斤欣欽琴禁禽筋緊芹菌衿襟謹近金吟銀九倶句区狗玖矩苦躯駆駈駒具愚虞喰空偶寓遇隅串櫛釧屑屈掘窟沓靴轡窪熊隈粂栗繰桑鍬勲君薫訓群軍郡卦袈祁係傾刑兄啓圭珪型契形径恵慶慧憩掲携敬景桂渓畦稽系経継繋罫茎荊蛍計詣警軽頚鶏芸迎鯨劇戟撃激隙桁傑欠決潔穴結血訣月件倹倦健兼券剣喧圏堅嫌建憲懸拳捲検権牽犬献研硯絹県肩見謙賢軒遣鍵険顕験鹸元原厳幻弦減源玄現絃舷言諺限乎個古呼固姑孤己庫弧戸故枯湖狐糊袴股胡菰虎誇跨鈷雇顧鼓五互伍午呉吾娯後御悟梧檎瑚碁語誤護醐乞鯉交佼侯候倖光公功効勾厚口向后喉坑垢好孔孝宏工巧巷幸広庚康弘恒慌抗拘控攻昂晃更杭校梗構江洪浩港溝甲皇硬稿糠紅紘絞綱耕考肯肱腔膏航荒行衡講貢購郊酵鉱砿鋼閤降項香高鴻剛劫号合壕拷濠豪轟麹克刻告国穀酷鵠黒獄漉腰甑忽惚骨狛込此頃今困坤墾婚恨懇昏昆根梱混痕紺艮魂些佐叉唆嵯左差査沙瑳砂詐鎖裟坐座挫債催再最哉塞妻宰彩才採栽歳済災采犀砕砦祭斎細菜裁載際剤在材罪財冴坂阪堺榊肴咲崎埼碕鷺作削咋搾昨朔柵窄策索錯桜鮭笹匙冊刷察拶撮擦札殺薩雑皐鯖捌錆鮫皿晒三傘参山惨撒散桟燦珊産算纂蚕讃賛酸餐斬暫残仕仔伺使刺司史嗣四士始姉姿子屍市師志思指支孜斯施旨枝止死氏獅祉私糸紙紫肢脂至視詞詩試誌諮資賜雌飼歯事似侍児字寺慈持時次滋治爾璽痔磁示而耳自蒔辞汐鹿式識鴫竺軸宍雫七叱執失嫉室悉湿漆疾質実蔀篠偲柴芝屡蕊縞舎写射捨赦斜煮社紗者謝車遮蛇邪借勺尺杓灼爵酌釈錫若寂弱惹主取守手朱殊狩珠種腫趣酒首儒受呪寿授樹綬需囚収周宗就州修愁拾洲秀秋終繍習臭舟蒐衆襲讐蹴輯週酋酬集醜什住充十従戎柔汁渋獣縦重銃叔夙宿淑祝縮粛塾熟出術述俊峻春瞬竣舜駿准循旬楯殉淳準潤盾純巡遵醇順処初所暑曙渚庶緒署書薯藷諸助叙女序徐恕鋤除傷償勝匠升召哨商唱嘗奨妾娼宵将小少尚庄床廠彰承抄招掌捷昇昌昭晶松梢樟樵沼消渉湘焼焦照症省硝礁祥称章笑粧紹肖菖蒋蕉衝裳訟証詔詳象賞醤鉦鍾鐘障鞘上丈丞乗冗剰城場壌嬢常情擾条杖浄状畳穣蒸譲醸錠嘱埴飾拭植殖燭織職色触食蝕辱尻伸信侵唇娠寝審心慎振新晋森榛浸深申疹真神秦紳臣芯薪親診身辛進針震人仁刃塵壬尋甚尽腎訊迅陣靭笥諏須酢図厨逗吹垂帥推水炊睡粋翠衰遂酔錐錘随瑞髄崇嵩数枢趨雛据杉椙菅頗雀裾澄摺寸世瀬畝是凄制勢姓征性成政整星晴棲栖正清牲生盛精聖声製西誠誓請逝醒青静斉税脆隻席惜戚斥昔析石積籍績脊責赤跡蹟碩切拙接摂折設窃節説雪絶舌蝉仙先千占宣専尖川戦扇撰栓栴泉浅洗染潜煎煽旋穿箭線繊羨腺舛船薦詮賎践選遷銭銑閃鮮前善漸然全禅繕膳糎噌塑岨措曾曽楚狙疏疎礎祖租粗素組蘇訴阻遡鼠僧創双叢倉喪壮奏爽宋層匝惣想捜掃挿掻操早曹巣槍槽漕燥争痩相窓糟総綜聡草荘葬蒼藻装走送遭鎗霜騒像増憎臓蔵贈造促側則即息捉束測足速俗属賊族続卒袖其揃存孫尊損村遜他多太汰詑唾堕妥惰打柁舵楕陀駄騨体堆対耐岱帯待怠態戴替泰滞胎腿苔袋貸退逮隊黛鯛代台大第醍題鷹滝瀧卓啄宅托択拓沢濯琢託鐸濁諾茸凧蛸只叩但達辰奪脱巽竪辿棚谷狸鱈樽誰丹単嘆坦担探旦歎淡湛炭短端箪綻耽胆蛋誕鍛団壇弾断暖檀段男談値知地弛恥智池痴稚置致蜘遅馳築畜竹筑蓄逐秩窒茶嫡着中仲宙忠抽昼柱注虫衷註酎鋳駐樗瀦猪苧著貯丁兆凋喋寵帖帳庁弔張彫徴懲挑暢朝潮牒町眺聴脹腸蝶調諜超跳銚長頂鳥勅捗直朕沈珍賃鎮陳津墜椎槌追鎚痛通塚栂掴槻佃漬柘辻蔦綴鍔椿潰坪壷嬬紬爪吊釣鶴亭低停偵剃貞呈堤定帝底庭廷弟悌抵挺提梯汀碇禎程締艇訂諦蹄逓邸鄭釘鼎泥摘擢敵滴的笛適鏑溺哲徹撤轍迭鉄典填天展店添纏甜貼転顛点伝殿澱田電兎吐堵塗妬屠徒斗杜渡登菟賭途都鍍砥砺努度土奴怒倒党冬凍刀唐塔塘套宕島嶋悼投搭東桃梼棟盗淘湯涛灯燈当痘祷等答筒糖統到董蕩藤討謄豆踏逃透鐙陶頭騰闘働動同堂導憧撞洞瞳童胴萄道銅峠鴇匿得徳涜特督禿篤毒独読栃橡凸突椴届鳶苫寅酉瀞噸屯惇敦沌豚遁頓呑曇鈍奈那内乍凪薙謎灘捺鍋楢馴縄畷南楠軟難汝二尼弐迩匂賑肉虹廿日乳入如尿韮任妊忍認濡禰祢寧葱猫熱年念捻撚燃粘乃廼之埜嚢悩濃納能脳膿農覗蚤巴把播覇杷波派琶破婆罵芭馬俳廃拝排敗杯盃牌背肺輩配倍培媒梅楳煤狽買売賠陪這蝿秤矧萩伯剥博拍柏泊白箔粕舶薄迫曝漠爆縛莫駁麦函箱硲箸肇筈櫨幡肌畑畠八鉢溌発醗髪伐罰抜筏閥鳩噺塙蛤隼伴判半反叛帆搬斑板氾汎版犯班畔繁般藩販範釆煩頒飯挽晩番盤磐蕃蛮匪卑否妃庇彼悲扉批披斐比泌疲皮碑秘緋罷肥被誹費避非飛樋簸備尾微枇毘琵眉美鼻柊稗匹疋髭彦膝菱肘弼必畢筆逼桧姫媛紐百謬俵彪標氷漂瓢票表評豹廟描病秒苗錨鋲蒜蛭鰭品彬斌浜瀕貧賓頻敏瓶不付埠夫婦富冨布府怖扶敷斧普浮父符腐膚芙譜負賦赴阜附侮撫武舞葡蕪部封楓風葺蕗伏副復幅服福腹複覆淵弗払沸仏物鮒分吻噴墳憤扮焚奮粉糞紛雰文聞丙併兵塀幣平弊柄並蔽閉陛米頁僻壁癖碧別瞥蔑箆偏変片篇編辺返遍便勉娩弁鞭保舗鋪圃捕歩甫補輔穂募墓慕戊暮母簿菩倣俸包呆報奉宝峰峯崩庖抱捧放方朋法泡烹砲縫胞芳萌蓬蜂褒訪豊邦鋒飽鳳鵬乏亡傍剖坊妨帽忘忙房暴望某棒冒紡肪膨謀貌貿鉾防吠頬北僕卜墨撲朴牧睦穆釦勃没殆堀幌奔本翻凡盆摩磨魔麻埋妹昧枚毎哩槙幕膜枕鮪柾鱒桝亦俣又抹末沫迄侭繭麿万慢満漫蔓味未魅巳箕岬密蜜湊蓑稔脈妙粍民眠務夢無牟矛霧鵡椋婿娘冥名命明盟迷銘鳴姪牝滅免棉綿緬面麺摸模茂妄孟毛猛盲網耗蒙儲木黙目杢勿餅尤戻籾貰問悶紋門匁也冶夜爺耶野弥矢厄役約薬訳躍靖柳薮鑓愉愈油癒諭輸唯佑優勇友宥幽悠憂揖有柚湧涌猶猷由祐裕誘遊邑郵雄融夕予余与誉輿預傭幼妖容庸揚揺擁曜楊様洋溶熔用窯羊耀葉蓉要謡踊遥陽養慾抑欲沃浴翌翼淀羅螺裸来莱頼雷洛絡落酪乱卵嵐欄濫藍蘭覧利吏履李梨理璃痢裏裡里離陸律率立葎掠略劉流溜琉留硫粒隆竜龍侶慮旅虜了亮僚両凌寮料梁涼猟療瞭稜糧良諒遼量陵領力緑倫厘林淋燐琳臨輪隣鱗麟瑠塁涙累類令伶例冷励嶺怜玲礼苓鈴隷零霊麗齢暦歴列劣烈裂廉恋憐漣煉簾練聯蓮連錬呂魯櫓炉賂路露労婁廊弄朗楼榔浪漏牢狼篭老聾蝋郎六麓禄肋録論倭和話歪賄脇惑枠鷲亙亘鰐詫藁蕨椀湾碗腕弌丐丕个丱丶丼丿乂乖乘亂亅豫亊舒弍于亞亟亠亢亰亳亶从仍仄仆仂仗仞仭仟价伉佚估佛佝佗佇佶侈侏侘佻佩佰侑佯來侖儘俔俟俎俘俛俑俚俐俤俥倚倨倔倪倥倅伜俶倡倩倬俾俯們倆偃假會偕偐偈做偖偬偸傀傚傅傴傲僉僊傳僂僖僞僥僭僣僮價僵儉儁儂儖儕儔儚儡儺儷儼儻儿兀兒兌兔兢竸兩兪兮冀冂囘册冉冏冑冓冕冖冤冦冢冩冪冫决冱冲冰况冽凅凉凛几處凩凭凰凵凾刄刋刔刎刧刪刮刳刹剏剄剋剌剞剔剪剴剩剳剿剽劍劔劒剱劈劑辨辧劬劭劼劵勁勍勗勞勣勦飭勠勳勵勸勹匆匈甸匍匐匏匕匚匣匯匱匳匸區卆卅丗卉卍凖卞卩卮夘卻卷厂厖厠厦厥厮厰厶參簒雙叟曼燮叮叨叭叺吁吽呀听吭吼吮吶吩吝呎咏呵咎呟呱呷呰咒呻咀呶咄咐咆哇咢咸咥咬哄哈咨咫哂咤咾咼哘哥哦唏唔哽哮哭哺哢唹啀啣啌售啜啅啖啗唸唳啝喙喀咯喊喟啻啾喘喞單啼喃喩喇喨嗚嗅嗟嗄嗜嗤嗔嘔嗷嘖嗾嗽嘛嗹噎噐營嘴嘶嘲嘸噫噤嘯噬噪嚆嚀嚊嚠嚔嚏嚥嚮嚶嚴囂嚼囁囃囀囈囎囑囓囗囮囹圀囿圄圉圈國圍圓團圖嗇圜圦圷圸坎圻址坏坩埀垈坡坿垉垓垠垳垤垪垰埃埆埔埒埓堊埖埣堋堙堝塲堡塢塋塰毀塒堽塹墅墹墟墫墺壞墻墸墮壅壓壑壗壙壘壥壜壤壟壯壺壹壻壼壽夂夊夐夛梦夥夬夭夲夸夾竒奕奐奎奚奘奢奠奧奬奩奸妁妝佞侫妣妲姆姨姜妍姙姚娥娟娑娜娉娚婀婬婉娵娶婢婪媚媼媾嫋嫂媽嫣嫗嫦嫩嫖嫺嫻嬌嬋嬖嬲嫐嬪嬶嬾孃孅孀孑孕孚孛孥孩孰孳孵學斈孺宀它宦宸寃寇寉寔寐寤實寢寞寥寫寰寶寳尅將專對尓尠尢尨尸尹屁屆屎屓屐屏孱屬屮乢屶屹岌岑岔妛岫岻岶岼岷峅岾峇峙峩峽峺峭嶌峪崋崕崗嵜崟崛崑崔崢崚崙崘嵌嵒嵎嵋嵬嵳嵶嶇嶄嶂嶢嶝嶬嶮嶽嶐嶷嶼巉巍巓巒巖巛巫已巵帋帚帙帑帛帶帷幄幃幀幎幗幔幟幢幤幇幵并幺麼广庠廁廂廈廐廏廖廣廝廚廛廢廡廨廩廬廱廳廰廴廸廾弃弉彝彜弋弑弖弩弭弸彁彈彌彎弯彑彖彗彙彡彭彳彷徃徂彿徊很徑徇從徙徘徠徨徭徼忖忻忤忸忱忝悳忿怡恠怙怐怩怎怱怛怕怫怦怏怺恚恁恪恷恟恊恆恍恣恃恤恂恬恫恙悁悍惧悃悚悄悛悖悗悒悧悋惡悸惠惓悴忰悽惆悵惘慍愕愆惶惷愀惴惺愃愡惻惱愍愎慇愾愨愧慊愿愼愬愴愽慂慄慳慷慘慙慚慫慴慯慥慱慟慝慓慵憙憖憇憬憔憚憊憑憫憮懌懊應懷懈懃懆憺懋罹懍懦懣懶懺懴懿懽懼懾戀戈戉戍戌戔戛戞戡截戮戰戲戳扁扎扞扣扛扠扨扼抂抉找抒抓抖拔抃抔拗拑抻拏拿拆擔拈拜拌拊拂拇抛拉挌拮拱挧挂挈拯拵捐挾捍搜捏掖掎掀掫捶掣掏掉掟掵捫捩掾揩揀揆揣揉插揶揄搖搴搆搓搦搶攝搗搨搏摧摯摶摎攪撕撓撥撩撈撼據擒擅擇撻擘擂擱擧舉擠擡抬擣擯攬擶擴擲擺攀擽攘攜攅攤攣攫攴攵攷收攸畋效敖敕敍敘敞敝敲數斂斃變斛斟斫斷旃旆旁旄旌旒旛旙无旡旱杲昊昃旻杳昵昶昴昜晏晄晉晁晞晝晤晧晨晟晢晰暃暈暎暉暄暘暝曁暹曉暾暼曄暸曖曚曠昿曦曩曰曵曷朏朖朞朦朧霸朮朿朶杁朸朷杆杞杠杙杣杤枉杰枩杼杪枌枋枦枡枅枷柯枴柬枳柩枸柤柞柝柢柮枹柎柆柧檜栞框栩桀桍栲桎梳栫桙档桷桿梟梏梭梔條梛梃檮梹桴梵梠梺椏梍桾椁棊椈棘椢椦棡椌棍棔棧棕椶椒椄棗棣椥棹棠棯椨椪椚椣椡棆楹楷楜楸楫楔楾楮椹楴椽楙椰楡楞楝榁楪榲榮槐榿槁槓榾槎寨槊槝榻槃榧樮榑榠榜榕榴槞槨樂樛槿權槹槲槧樅榱樞槭樔槫樊樒櫁樣樓橄樌橲樶橸橇橢橙橦橈樸樢檐檍檠檄檢檣檗蘗檻櫃櫂檸檳檬櫞櫑櫟檪櫚櫪櫻欅蘖櫺欒欖鬱欟欸欷盜欹飮歇歃歉歐歙歔歛歟歡歸歹歿殀殄殃殍殘殕殞殤殪殫殯殲殱殳殷殼毆毋毓毟毬毫毳毯麾氈氓气氛氤氣汞汕汢汪沂沍沚沁沛汾汨汳沒沐泄泱泓沽泗泅泝沮沱沾沺泛泯泙泪洟衍洶洫洽洸洙洵洳洒洌浣涓浤浚浹浙涎涕濤涅淹渕渊涵淇淦涸淆淬淞淌淨淒淅淺淙淤淕淪淮渭湮渮渙湲湟渾渣湫渫湶湍渟湃渺湎渤滿渝游溂溪溘滉溷滓溽溯滄溲滔滕溏溥滂溟潁漑灌滬滸滾漿滲漱滯漲滌漾漓滷澆潺潸澁澀潯潛濳潭澂潼潘澎澑濂潦澳澣澡澤澹濆澪濟濕濬濔濘濱濮濛瀉瀋濺瀑瀁瀏濾瀛瀚潴瀝瀘瀟瀰瀾瀲灑灣炙炒炯烱炬炸炳炮烟烋烝烙焉烽焜焙煥煕熈煦煢煌煖煬熏燻熄熕熨熬燗熹熾燒燉燔燎燠燬燧燵燼燹燿爍爐爛爨爭爬爰爲爻爼爿牀牆牋牘牴牾犂犁犇犒犖犢犧犹犲狃狆狄狎狒狢狠狡狹狷倏猗猊猜猖猝猴猯猩猥猾獎獏默獗獪獨獰獸獵獻獺珈玳珎玻珀珥珮珞璢琅瑯琥珸琲琺瑕琿瑟瑙瑁瑜瑩瑰瑣瑪瑶瑾璋璞璧瓊瓏瓔珱瓠瓣瓧瓩瓮瓲瓰瓱瓸瓷甄甃甅甌甎甍甕甓甞甦甬甼畄畍畊畉畛畆畚畩畤畧畫畭畸當疆疇畴疊疉疂疔疚疝疥疣痂疳痃疵疽疸疼疱痍痊痒痙痣痞痾痿痼瘁痰痺痲痳瘋瘍瘉瘟瘧瘠瘡瘢瘤瘴瘰瘻癇癈癆癜癘癡癢癨癩癪癧癬癰癲癶癸發皀皃皈皋皎皖皓皙皚皰皴皸皹皺盂盍盖盒盞盡盥盧盪蘯盻眈眇眄眩眤眞眥眦眛眷眸睇睚睨睫睛睥睿睾睹瞎瞋瞑瞠瞞瞰瞶瞹瞿瞼瞽瞻矇矍矗矚矜矣矮矼砌砒礦砠礪硅碎硴碆硼碚碌碣碵碪碯磑磆磋磔碾碼磅磊磬磧磚磽磴礇礒礑礙礬礫祀祠祗祟祚祕祓祺祿禊禝禧齋禪禮禳禹禺秉秕秧秬秡秣稈稍稘稙稠稟禀稱稻稾稷穃穗穉穡穢穩龝穰穹穽窈窗窕窘窖窩竈窰窶竅竄窿邃竇竊竍竏竕竓站竚竝竡竢竦竭竰笂笏笊笆笳笘笙笞笵笨笶筐筺笄筍笋筌筅筵筥筴筧筰筱筬筮箝箘箟箍箜箚箋箒箏筝箙篋篁篌篏箴篆篝篩簑簔篦篥籠簀簇簓篳篷簗簍篶簣簧簪簟簷簫簽籌籃籔籏籀籐籘籟籤籖籥籬籵粃粐粤粭粢粫粡粨粳粲粱粮粹粽糀糅糂糘糒糜糢鬻糯糲糴糶糺紆紂紜紕紊絅絋紮紲紿紵絆絳絖絎絲絨絮絏絣經綉絛綏絽綛綺綮綣綵緇綽綫總綢綯緜綸綟綰緘緝緤緞緻緲緡縅縊縣縡縒縱縟縉縋縢繆繦縻縵縹繃縷縲縺繧繝繖繞繙繚繹繪繩繼繻纃緕繽辮繿纈纉續纒纐纓纔纖纎纛纜缸缺罅罌罍罎罐网罕罔罘罟罠罨罩罧罸羂羆羃羈羇羌羔羞羝羚羣羯羲羹羮羶羸譱翅翆翊翕翔翡翦翩翳翹飜耆耄耋耒耘耙耜耡耨耿耻聊聆聒聘聚聟聢聨聳聲聰聶聹聽聿肄肆肅肛肓肚肭冐肬胛胥胙胝胄胚胖脉胯胱脛脩脣脯腋隋腆脾腓腑胼腱腮腥腦腴膃膈膊膀膂膠膕膤膣腟膓膩膰膵膾膸膽臀臂膺臉臍臑臙臘臈臚臟臠臧臺臻臾舁舂舅與舊舍舐舖舩舫舸舳艀艙艘艝艚艟艤艢艨艪艫舮艱艷艸艾芍芒芫芟芻芬苡苣苟苒苴苳苺莓范苻苹苞茆苜茉苙茵茴茖茲茱荀茹荐荅茯茫茗茘莅莚莪莟莢莖茣莎莇莊荼莵荳荵莠莉莨菴萓菫菎菽萃菘萋菁菷萇菠菲萍萢萠莽萸蔆菻葭萪萼蕚蒄葷葫蒭葮蒂葩葆萬葯葹萵蓊葢蒹蒿蒟蓙蓍蒻蓚蓐蓁蓆蓖蒡蔡蓿蓴蔗蔘蔬蔟蔕蔔蓼蕀蕣蕘蕈蕁蘂蕋蕕薀薤薈薑薊薨蕭薔薛藪薇薜蕷蕾薐藉薺藏薹藐藕藝藥藜藹蘊蘓蘋藾藺蘆蘢蘚蘰蘿虍乕虔號虧虱蚓蚣蚩蚪蚋蚌蚶蚯蛄蛆蚰蛉蠣蚫蛔蛞蛩蛬蛟蛛蛯蜒蜆蜈蜀蜃蛻蜑蜉蜍蛹蜊蜴蜿蜷蜻蜥蜩蜚蝠蝟蝸蝌蝎蝴蝗蝨蝮蝙蝓蝣蝪蠅螢螟螂螯蟋螽蟀蟐雖螫蟄螳蟇蟆螻蟯蟲蟠蠏蠍蟾蟶蟷蠎蟒蠑蠖蠕蠢蠡蠱蠶蠹蠧蠻衄衂衒衙衞衢衫袁衾袞衵衽袵衲袂袗袒袮袙袢袍袤袰袿袱裃裄裔裘裙裝裹褂裼裴裨裲褄褌褊褓襃褞褥褪褫襁襄褻褶褸襌褝襠襞襦襤襭襪襯襴襷襾覃覈覊覓覘覡覩覦覬覯覲覺覽覿觀觚觜觝觧觴觸訃訖訐訌訛訝訥訶詁詛詒詆詈詼詭詬詢誅誂誄誨誡誑誥誦誚誣諄諍諂諚諫諳諧諤諱謔諠諢諷諞諛謌謇謚諡謖謐謗謠謳鞫謦謫謾謨譁譌譏譎證譖譛譚譫譟譬譯譴譽讀讌讎讒讓讖讙讚谺豁谿豈豌豎豐豕豢豬豸豺貂貉貅貊貍貎貔豼貘戝貭貪貽貲貳貮貶賈賁賤賣賚賽賺賻贄贅贊贇贏贍贐齎贓賍贔贖赧赭赱赳趁趙跂趾趺跏跚跖跌跛跋跪跫跟跣跼踈踉跿踝踞踐踟蹂踵踰踴蹊蹇蹉蹌蹐蹈蹙蹤蹠踪蹣蹕蹶蹲蹼躁躇躅躄躋躊躓躑躔躙躪躡躬躰軆躱躾軅軈軋軛軣軼軻軫軾輊輅輕輒輙輓輜輟輛輌輦輳輻輹轅轂輾轌轉轆轎轗轜轢轣轤辜辟辣辭辯辷迚迥迢迪迯邇迴逅迹迺逑逕逡逍逞逖逋逧逶逵逹迸遏遐遑遒逎遉逾遖遘遞遨遯遶隨遲邂遽邁邀邊邉邏邨邯邱邵郢郤扈郛鄂鄒鄙鄲鄰酊酖酘酣酥酩酳酲醋醉醂醢醫醯醪醵醴醺釀釁釉釋釐釖釟釡釛釼釵釶鈞釿鈔鈬鈕鈑鉞鉗鉅鉉鉤鉈銕鈿鉋鉐銜銖銓銛鉚鋏銹銷鋩錏鋺鍄錮錙錢錚錣錺錵錻鍜鍠鍼鍮鍖鎰鎬鎭鎔鎹鏖鏗鏨鏥鏘鏃鏝鏐鏈鏤鐚鐔鐓鐃鐇鐐鐶鐫鐵鐡鐺鑁鑒鑄鑛鑠鑢鑞鑪鈩鑰鑵鑷鑽鑚鑼鑾钁鑿閂閇閊閔閖閘閙閠閨閧閭閼閻閹閾闊濶闃闍闌闕闔闖關闡闥闢阡阨阮阯陂陌陏陋陷陜陞陝陟陦陲陬隍隘隕隗險隧隱隲隰隴隶隸隹雎雋雉雍襍雜霍雕雹霄霆霈霓霎霑霏霖霙霤霪霰霹霽霾靄靆靈靂靉靜靠靤靦靨勒靫靱靹鞅靼鞁靺鞆鞋鞏鞐鞜鞨鞦鞣鞳鞴韃韆韈韋韜韭齏韲竟韶韵頏頌頸頤頡頷頽顆顏顋顫顯顰顱顴顳颪颯颱颶飄飃飆飩飫餃餉餒餔餘餡餝餞餤餠餬餮餽餾饂饉饅饐饋饑饒饌饕馗馘馥馭馮馼駟駛駝駘駑駭駮駱駲駻駸騁騏騅駢騙騫騷驅驂驀驃騾驕驍驛驗驟驢驥驤驩驫驪骭骰骼髀髏髑髓體髞髟髢髣髦髯髫髮髴髱髷髻鬆鬘鬚鬟鬢鬣鬥鬧鬨鬩鬪鬮鬯鬲魄魃魏魍魎魑魘魴鮓鮃鮑鮖鮗鮟鮠鮨鮴鯀鯊鮹鯆鯏鯑鯒鯣鯢鯤鯔鯡鰺鯲鯱鯰鰕鰔鰉鰓鰌鰆鰈鰒鰊鰄鰮鰛鰥鰤鰡鰰鱇鰲鱆鰾鱚鱠鱧鱶鱸鳧鳬鳰鴉鴈鳫鴃鴆鴪鴦鶯鴣鴟鵄鴕鴒鵁鴿鴾鵆鵈鵝鵞鵤鵑鵐鵙鵲鶉鶇鶫鵯鵺鶚鶤鶩鶲鷄鷁鶻鶸鶺鷆鷏鷂鷙鷓鷸鷦鷭鷯鷽鸚鸛鸞鹵鹹鹽麁麈麋麌麒麕麑麝麥麩麸麪麭靡黌黎黏黐黔黜點黝黠黥黨黯黴黶黷黹黻黼黽鼇鼈皷鼕鼡鼬鼾齊齒齔齣齟齠齡齦齧齬齪齷齲齶龕龜龠堯槇遙瑤凜熙纊褜鍈銈蓜俉炻昱棈鋹曻彅丨仡仼伀伃伹佖侒侊侚侔俍偀倢俿倞偆偰偂傔僴僘兊兤冝冾凬刕劜劦勀勛匀匇匤卲厓厲叝﨎咜咊咩哿喆坙坥垬埈埇﨏塚增墲夋奓奛奝奣妤妺孖寀甯寘寬尞岦岺峵崧嵓﨑嵂嵭嶸嶹巐弡弴彧德忞恝悅悊惞惕愠惲愑愷愰憘戓抦揵摠撝擎敎昀昕昻昉昮昞昤晥晗晙晴晳暙暠暲暿曺朎朗杦枻桒柀栁桄棏﨓楨﨔榘槢樰橫橆橳橾櫢櫤毖氿汜沆汯泚洄涇浯涖涬淏淸淲淼渹湜渧渼溿澈澵濵瀅瀇瀨炅炫焏焄煜煆煇凞燁燾犱犾猤猪獷玽珉珖珣珒琇珵琦琪琩琮瑢璉璟甁畯皂皜皞皛皦益睆劯砡硎硤硺礰礼神祥禔福禛竑竧靖竫箞精絈絜綷綠緖繒罇羡羽茁荢荿菇菶葈蒴蕓蕙蕫﨟薰蘒﨡蠇裵訒訷詹誧誾諟諸諶譓譿賰賴贒赶﨣軏﨤逸遧郞都鄕鄧釚釗釞釭釮釤釥鈆鈐鈊鈺鉀鈼鉎鉙鉑鈹鉧銧鉷鉸鋧鋗鋙鋐﨧鋕鋠鋓錥錡鋻﨨錞鋿錝錂鍰鍗鎤鏆鏞鏸鐱鑅鑈閒隆﨩隝隯霳霻靃靍靏靑靕顗顥飯飼餧館馞驎髙髜魵魲鮏鮱鮻鰀鵰鵫鶴鸙黑ⅰⅱⅲⅳⅴⅵⅶⅷⅸⅹ￢￤＇＂ⅰⅱⅲⅳⅴⅵⅶⅷⅸⅹⅠⅡⅢⅣⅤⅥⅦⅧⅨⅩ￢￤＇＂㈱№℡∵纊褜鍈銈蓜俉炻昱棈鋹曻彅丨仡仼伀伃伹佖侒侊侚侔俍偀倢俿倞偆偰偂傔僴僘兊兤冝冾凬刕劜劦勀勛匀匇匤卲厓厲叝﨎咜咊咩哿喆坙坥垬埈埇﨏塚增墲夋奓奛奝奣妤妺孖寀甯寘寬尞岦岺峵崧嵓﨑嵂嵭嶸嶹巐弡弴彧德忞恝悅悊惞惕愠惲愑愷愰憘戓抦揵摠撝擎敎昀昕昻昉昮昞昤晥晗晙晴晳暙暠暲暿曺朎朗杦枻桒柀栁桄棏﨓楨﨔榘槢樰橫橆橳橾櫢櫤毖氿汜沆汯泚洄涇浯涖涬淏淸淲淼渹湜渧渼溿澈澵濵瀅瀇瀨炅炫焏焄煜煆煇凞燁燾犱犾猤猪獷玽珉珖珣珒琇珵琦琪琩琮瑢璉璟甁畯皂皜皞皛皦益睆劯砡硎硤硺礰礼神祥禔福禛竑竧靖竫箞精絈絜綷綠緖繒罇羡羽茁荢荿菇菶葈蒴蕓蕙蕫﨟薰蘒﨡蠇裵訒訷詹誧誾諟諸諶譓譿賰賴贒赶﨣軏﨤逸遧郞都鄕鄧釚釗釞釭釮釤釥鈆鈐鈊鈺鉀鈼鉎鉙鉑鈹鉧銧鉷鉸鋧鋗鋙鋐﨧鋕鋠鋓錥錡鋻﨨錞鋿錝錂鍰鍗鎤鏆鏞鏸鐱鑅鑈閒隆﨩隝隯霳霻靃靍靏靑靕顗顥飯飼餧館馞驎髙髜魵魲鮏鮱鮻鰀鵰鵫鶴鸙黑ぁあぃいぅうぇえぉおかがきぎくぐけげこごさざしじすずせぜそぞただちぢっつづてでとどなにぬねのはばぱひびぴふぶぷへべぺほぼぽまみむめもゃやゅゆょよらりるれろゎわゐゑをんァアィイゥウェエォオカガキギクグケゲコゴサザシジスズセゼソゾタダチヂッツヅテデトドナニヌネノハバパヒビピフブプヘベペホボポマミムメモャヤュユョヨラリルレロヮワヰヱヲンヴヵヶ０１２３４５６７８９①②③④⑤⑥⑦⑧⑨⑩⑪⑫⑬⑭⑮⑯⑰⑱⑲⑳ⅠⅡⅢⅣⅤⅥⅦⅧⅨⅩ㍉㌔㌢㍍㌘㌧㌃㌶㍑㍗㌍㌦㌣㌫㍊㌻㎜㎝㎞㎎㎏㏄㎡㍻〝〟№㏍℡㊤㊥㊦㊧㊨㈱㈲㈹㍾㍽㍼亜唖娃阿哀愛挨姶逢葵茜穐悪握渥旭葦芦鯵梓圧斡扱宛姐虻飴絢綾鮎或粟袷安庵按暗案闇鞍杏以伊位依偉囲夷委威尉惟意慰易椅為畏異移維緯胃萎衣謂違遺医井亥域育郁磯一壱溢逸稲茨芋鰯允印咽員因姻引飲淫胤蔭院陰隠韻吋右宇烏羽迂雨卯鵜窺丑碓臼渦嘘唄欝蔚鰻姥厩浦瓜閏噂云運雲荏餌叡営嬰影映曳栄永泳洩瑛盈穎頴英衛詠鋭液疫益駅悦謁越閲榎厭円園堰奄宴延怨掩援沿演炎焔煙燕猿縁艶苑薗遠鉛鴛塩於汚甥凹央奥往応押旺横欧殴王翁襖鴬鴎黄岡沖荻億屋憶臆桶牡乙俺卸恩温穏音下化仮何伽価佳加可嘉夏嫁家寡科暇果架歌河火珂禍禾稼箇花苛茄荷華菓蝦課嘩貨迦過霞蚊俄峨我牙画臥芽蛾賀雅餓駕介会解回塊壊廻快怪悔恢懐戒拐改魁晦械海灰界皆絵芥蟹開階貝凱劾外咳害崖慨概涯碍蓋街該鎧骸浬馨蛙垣柿蛎鈎劃嚇各廓拡撹格核殻獲確穫覚角赫較郭閣隔革学岳楽額顎掛笠樫橿梶鰍潟割喝恰括活渇滑葛褐轄且鰹叶椛樺鞄株兜竃蒲釜鎌噛鴨栢茅萱粥刈苅瓦乾侃冠寒刊勘勧巻喚堪姦完官寛干幹患感慣憾換敢柑桓棺款歓汗漢澗潅環甘監看竿管簡緩缶翰肝艦莞観諌貫還鑑間閑関陥韓館舘丸含岸巌玩癌眼岩翫贋雁頑顔願企伎危喜器基奇嬉寄岐希幾忌揮机旗既期棋棄機帰毅気汽畿祈季稀紀徽規記貴起軌輝飢騎鬼亀偽儀妓宜戯技擬欺犠疑祇義蟻誼議掬菊鞠吉吃喫桔橘詰砧杵黍却客脚虐逆丘久仇休及吸宮弓急救朽求汲泣灸球究窮笈級糾給旧牛去居巨拒拠挙渠虚許距鋸漁禦魚亨享京供侠僑兇競共凶協匡卿叫喬境峡強彊怯恐恭挟教橋況狂狭矯胸脅興蕎郷鏡響饗驚仰凝尭暁業局曲極玉桐粁僅勤均巾錦斤欣欽琴禁禽筋緊芹菌衿襟謹近金吟銀九倶句区狗玖矩苦躯駆駈駒具愚虞喰空偶寓遇隅串櫛釧屑屈掘窟沓靴轡窪熊隈粂栗繰桑鍬勲君薫訓群軍郡卦袈祁係傾刑兄啓圭珪型契形径恵慶慧憩掲携敬景桂渓畦稽系経継繋罫茎荊蛍計詣警軽頚鶏芸迎鯨劇戟撃激隙桁傑欠決潔穴結血訣月件倹倦健兼券剣喧圏堅嫌建憲懸拳捲検権牽犬献研硯絹県肩見謙賢軒遣鍵険顕験鹸元原厳幻弦減源玄現絃舷言諺限乎個古呼固姑孤己庫弧戸故枯湖狐糊袴股胡菰虎誇跨鈷雇顧鼓五互伍午呉吾娯後御悟梧檎瑚碁語誤護醐乞鯉交佼侯候倖光公功効勾厚口向后喉坑垢好孔孝宏工巧巷幸広庚康弘恒慌抗拘控攻昂晃更杭校梗構江洪浩港溝甲皇硬稿糠紅紘絞綱耕考肯肱腔膏航荒行衡講貢購郊酵鉱砿鋼閤降項香高鴻剛劫号合壕拷濠豪轟麹克刻告国穀酷鵠黒獄漉腰甑忽惚骨狛込此頃今困坤墾婚恨懇昏昆根梱混痕紺艮魂些佐叉唆嵯左差査沙瑳砂詐鎖裟坐座挫債催再最哉塞妻宰彩才採栽歳済災采犀砕砦祭斎細菜裁載際剤在材罪財冴坂阪堺榊肴咲崎埼碕鷺作削咋搾昨朔柵窄策索錯桜鮭笹匙冊刷察拶撮擦札殺薩雑皐鯖捌錆鮫皿晒三傘参山惨撒散桟燦珊産算纂蚕讃賛酸餐斬暫残仕仔伺使刺司史嗣四士始姉姿子屍市師志思指支孜斯施旨枝止死氏獅祉私糸紙紫肢脂至視詞詩試誌諮資賜雌飼歯事似侍児字寺慈持時次滋治爾璽痔磁示而耳自蒔辞汐鹿式識鴫竺軸宍雫七叱執失嫉室悉湿漆疾質実蔀篠偲柴芝屡蕊縞舎写射捨赦斜煮社紗者謝車遮蛇邪借勺尺杓灼爵酌釈錫若寂弱惹主取守手朱殊狩珠種腫趣酒首儒受呪寿授樹綬需囚収周宗就州修愁拾洲秀秋終繍習臭舟蒐衆襲讐蹴輯週酋酬集醜什住充十従戎柔汁渋獣縦重銃叔夙宿淑祝縮粛塾熟出術述俊峻春瞬竣舜駿准循旬楯殉淳準潤盾純巡遵醇順処初所暑曙渚庶緒署書薯藷諸助叙女序徐恕鋤除傷償勝匠升召哨商唱嘗奨妾娼宵将小少尚庄床廠彰承抄招掌捷昇昌昭晶松梢樟樵沼消渉湘焼焦照症省硝礁祥称章笑粧紹肖菖蒋蕉衝裳訟証詔詳象賞醤鉦鍾鐘障鞘上丈丞乗冗剰城場壌嬢常情擾条杖浄状畳穣蒸譲醸錠嘱埴飾拭植殖燭織職色触食蝕辱尻伸信侵唇娠寝審心慎振新晋森榛浸深申疹真神秦紳臣芯薪親診身辛進針震人仁刃塵壬尋甚尽腎訊迅陣靭笥諏須酢図厨逗吹垂帥推水炊睡粋翠衰遂酔錐錘随瑞髄崇嵩数枢趨雛据杉椙菅頗雀裾澄摺寸世瀬畝是凄制勢姓征性成政整星晴棲栖正清牲生盛精聖声製西誠誓請逝醒青静斉税脆隻席惜戚斥昔析石積籍績脊責赤跡蹟碩切拙接摂折設窃節説雪絶舌蝉仙先千占宣専尖川戦扇撰栓栴泉浅洗染潜煎煽旋穿箭線繊羨腺舛船薦詮賎践選遷銭銑閃鮮前善漸然全禅繕膳糎噌塑岨措曾曽楚狙疏疎礎祖租粗素組蘇訴阻遡鼠僧創双叢倉喪壮奏爽宋層匝惣想捜掃挿掻操早曹巣槍槽漕燥争痩相窓糟総綜聡草荘葬蒼藻装走送遭鎗霜騒像増憎臓蔵贈造促側則即息捉束測足速俗属賊族続卒袖其揃存孫尊損村遜他多太汰詑唾堕妥惰打柁舵楕陀駄騨体堆対耐岱帯待怠態戴替泰滞胎腿苔袋貸退逮隊黛鯛代台大第醍題鷹滝瀧卓啄宅托択拓沢濯琢託鐸濁諾茸凧蛸只叩但達辰奪脱巽竪辿棚谷狸鱈樽誰丹単嘆坦担探旦歎淡湛炭短端箪綻耽胆蛋誕鍛団壇弾断暖檀段男談値知地弛恥智池痴稚置致蜘遅馳築畜竹筑蓄逐秩窒茶嫡着中仲宙忠抽昼柱注虫衷註酎鋳駐樗瀦猪苧著貯丁兆凋喋寵帖帳庁弔張彫徴懲挑暢朝潮牒町眺聴脹腸蝶調諜超跳銚長頂鳥勅捗直朕沈珍賃鎮陳津墜椎槌追鎚痛通塚栂掴槻佃漬柘辻蔦綴鍔椿潰坪壷嬬紬爪吊釣鶴亭低停偵剃貞呈堤定帝底庭廷弟悌抵挺提梯汀碇禎程締艇訂諦蹄逓邸鄭釘鼎泥摘擢敵滴的笛適鏑溺哲徹撤轍迭鉄典填天展店添纏甜貼転顛点伝殿澱田電兎吐堵塗妬屠徒斗杜渡登菟賭途都鍍砥砺努度土奴怒倒党冬凍刀唐塔塘套宕島嶋悼投搭東桃梼棟盗淘湯涛灯燈当痘祷等答筒糖統到董蕩藤討謄豆踏逃透鐙陶頭騰闘働動同堂導憧撞洞瞳童胴萄道銅峠鴇匿得徳涜特督禿篤毒独読栃橡凸突椴届鳶苫寅酉瀞噸屯惇敦沌豚遁頓呑曇鈍奈那内乍凪薙謎灘捺鍋楢馴縄畷南楠軟難汝二尼弐迩匂賑肉虹廿日乳入如尿韮任妊忍認濡禰祢寧葱猫熱年念捻撚燃粘乃廼之埜嚢悩濃納能脳膿農覗蚤巴把播覇杷波派琶破婆罵芭馬俳廃拝排敗杯盃牌背肺輩配倍培媒梅楳煤狽買売賠陪這蝿秤矧萩伯剥博拍柏泊白箔粕舶薄迫曝漠爆縛莫駁麦函箱硲箸肇筈櫨幡肌畑畠八鉢溌発醗髪伐罰抜筏閥鳩噺塙蛤隼伴判半反叛帆搬斑板氾汎版犯班畔繁般藩販範釆煩頒飯挽晩番盤磐蕃蛮匪卑否妃庇彼悲扉批披斐比泌疲皮碑秘緋罷肥被誹費避非飛樋簸備尾微枇毘琵眉美鼻柊稗匹疋髭彦膝菱肘弼必畢筆逼桧姫媛紐百謬俵彪標氷漂瓢票表評豹廟描病秒苗錨鋲蒜蛭鰭品彬斌浜瀕貧賓頻敏瓶不付埠夫婦富冨布府怖扶敷斧普浮父符腐膚芙譜負賦赴阜附侮撫武舞葡蕪部封楓風葺蕗伏副復幅服福腹複覆淵弗払沸仏物鮒分吻噴墳憤扮焚奮粉糞紛雰文聞丙併兵塀幣平弊柄並蔽閉陛米頁僻壁癖碧別瞥蔑箆偏変片篇編辺返遍便勉娩弁鞭保舗鋪圃捕歩甫補輔穂募墓慕戊暮母簿菩倣俸包呆報奉宝峰峯崩庖抱捧放方朋法泡烹砲縫胞芳萌蓬蜂褒訪豊邦鋒飽鳳鵬乏亡傍剖坊妨帽忘忙房暴望某棒冒紡肪膨謀貌貿鉾防吠頬北僕卜墨撲朴牧睦穆釦勃没殆堀幌奔本翻凡盆摩磨魔麻埋妹昧枚毎哩槙幕膜枕鮪柾鱒桝亦俣又抹末沫迄侭繭麿万慢満漫蔓味未魅巳箕岬密蜜湊蓑稔脈妙粍民眠務夢無牟矛霧鵡椋婿娘冥名命明盟迷銘鳴姪牝滅免棉綿緬面麺摸模茂妄孟毛猛盲網耗蒙儲木黙目杢勿餅尤戻籾貰問悶紋門匁也冶夜爺耶野弥矢厄役約薬訳躍靖柳薮鑓愉愈油癒諭輸唯佑優勇友宥幽悠憂揖有柚湧涌猶猷由祐裕誘遊邑郵雄融夕予余与誉輿預傭幼妖容庸揚揺擁曜楊様洋溶熔用窯羊耀葉蓉要謡踊遥陽養慾抑欲沃浴翌翼淀羅螺裸来莱頼雷洛絡落酪乱卵嵐欄濫藍蘭覧利吏履李梨理璃痢裏裡里離陸律率立葎掠略劉流溜琉留硫粒隆竜龍侶慮旅虜了亮僚両凌寮料梁涼猟療瞭稜糧良諒遼量陵領力緑倫厘林淋燐琳臨輪隣鱗麟瑠塁涙累類令伶例冷励嶺怜玲礼苓鈴隷零霊麗齢暦歴列劣烈裂廉恋憐漣煉簾練聯蓮連錬呂魯櫓炉賂路露労婁廊弄朗楼榔浪漏牢狼篭老聾蝋郎六麓禄肋録論倭和話歪賄脇惑枠鷲亙亘鰐詫藁蕨椀湾碗腕弌丐丕个丱丶丼丿乂乖乘亂亅豫亊舒弍于亞亟亠亢亰亳亶从仍仄仆仂仗仞仭仟价伉佚估佛佝佗佇佶侈侏侘佻佩佰侑佯來侖儘俔俟俎俘俛俑俚俐俤俥倚倨倔倪倥倅伜俶倡倩倬俾俯們倆偃假會偕偐偈做偖偬偸傀傚傅傴傲僉僊傳僂僖僞僥僭僣僮價僵儉儁儂儖儕儔儚儡儺儷儼儻儿兀兒兌兔兢竸兩兪兮冀冂囘册冉冏冑冓冕冖冤冦冢冩冪冫决冱冲冰况冽凅凉凛几處凩凭凰凵凾刄刋刔刎刧刪刮刳刹剏剄剋剌剞剔剪剴剩剳剿剽劍劔劒剱劈劑辨辧劬劭劼劵勁勍勗勞勣勦飭勠勳勵勸勹匆匈甸匍匐匏匕匚匣匯匱匳匸區卆卅丗卉卍凖卞卩卮夘卻卷厂厖厠厦厥厮厰厶參簒雙叟曼燮叮叨叭叺吁吽呀听吭吼吮吶吩吝呎咏呵咎呟呱呷呰咒呻咀呶咄咐咆哇咢咸咥咬哄哈咨咫哂咤咾咼哘哥哦唏唔哽哮哭哺哢唹啀啣啌售啜啅啖啗唸唳啝喙喀咯喊喟啻啾喘喞單啼喃喩喇喨嗚嗅嗟嗄嗜嗤嗔嘔嗷嘖嗾嗽嘛嗹噎噐營嘴嘶嘲嘸噫噤嘯噬噪嚆嚀嚊嚠嚔嚏嚥嚮嚶嚴囂嚼囁囃囀囈囎囑囓囗囮囹圀囿圄圉圈國圍圓團圖嗇圜圦圷圸坎圻址坏坩埀垈坡坿垉垓垠垳垤垪垰埃埆埔埒埓堊埖埣堋堙堝塲堡塢塋塰毀塒堽塹墅墹墟墫墺壞墻墸墮壅壓壑壗壙壘壥壜壤壟壯壺壹壻壼壽夂夊夐夛梦夥夬夭夲夸夾竒奕奐奎奚奘奢奠奧奬奩奸妁妝佞侫妣妲姆姨姜妍姙姚娥娟娑娜娉娚婀婬婉娵娶婢婪媚媼媾嫋嫂媽嫣嫗嫦嫩嫖嫺嫻嬌嬋嬖嬲嫐嬪嬶嬾孃孅孀孑孕孚孛孥孩孰孳孵學斈孺宀它宦宸寃寇寉寔寐寤實寢寞寥寫寰寶寳尅將專對尓尠尢尨尸尹屁屆屎屓屐屏孱屬屮乢屶屹岌岑岔妛岫岻岶岼岷峅岾峇峙峩峽峺峭嶌峪崋崕崗嵜崟崛崑崔崢崚崙崘嵌嵒嵎嵋嵬嵳嵶嶇嶄嶂嶢嶝嶬嶮嶽嶐嶷嶼巉巍巓巒巖巛巫已巵帋帚帙帑帛帶帷幄幃幀幎幗幔幟幢幤幇幵并幺麼广庠廁廂廈廐廏廖廣廝廚廛廢廡廨廩廬廱廳廰廴廸廾弃弉彝彜弋弑弖弩弭弸彁彈彌彎弯彑彖彗彙彡彭彳彷徃徂彿徊很徑徇從徙徘徠徨徭徼忖忻忤忸忱忝悳忿怡恠怙怐怩怎怱怛怕怫怦怏怺恚恁恪恷恟恊恆恍恣恃恤恂恬恫恙悁悍惧悃悚悄悛悖悗悒悧悋惡悸惠惓悴忰悽惆悵惘慍愕愆惶惷愀惴惺愃愡惻惱愍愎慇愾愨愧慊愿愼愬愴愽慂慄慳慷慘慙慚慫慴慯慥慱慟慝慓慵憙憖憇憬憔憚憊憑憫憮懌懊應懷懈懃懆憺懋罹懍懦懣懶懺懴懿懽懼懾戀戈戉戍戌戔戛戞戡截戮戰戲戳扁扎扞扣扛扠扨扼抂抉找抒抓抖拔抃抔拗拑抻拏拿拆擔拈拜拌拊拂拇抛拉挌拮拱挧挂挈拯拵捐挾捍搜捏掖掎掀掫捶掣掏掉掟掵捫捩掾揩揀揆揣揉插揶揄搖搴搆搓搦搶攝搗搨搏摧摯摶摎攪撕撓撥撩撈撼據擒擅擇撻擘擂擱擧舉擠擡抬擣擯攬擶擴擲擺攀擽攘攜攅攤攣攫攴攵攷收攸畋效敖敕敍敘敞敝敲數斂斃變斛斟斫斷旃旆旁旄旌旒旛旙无旡旱杲昊昃旻杳昵昶昴昜晏晄晉晁晞晝晤晧晨晟晢晰暃暈暎暉暄暘暝曁暹曉暾暼曄暸曖曚曠昿曦曩曰曵曷朏朖朞朦朧霸朮朿朶杁朸朷杆杞杠杙杣杤枉杰枩杼杪枌枋枦枡枅枷柯枴柬枳柩枸柤柞柝柢柮枹柎柆柧檜栞框栩桀桍栲桎梳栫桙档桷桿梟梏梭梔條梛梃檮梹桴梵梠梺椏梍桾椁棊椈棘椢椦棡椌棍棔棧棕椶椒椄棗棣椥棹棠棯椨椪椚椣椡棆楹楷楜楸楫楔楾楮椹楴椽楙椰楡楞楝榁楪榲榮槐榿槁槓榾槎寨槊槝榻槃榧樮榑榠榜榕榴槞槨樂樛槿權槹槲槧樅榱樞槭樔槫樊樒櫁樣樓橄樌橲樶橸橇橢橙橦橈樸樢檐檍檠檄檢檣檗蘗檻櫃櫂檸檳檬櫞櫑櫟檪櫚櫪櫻欅蘖櫺欒欖鬱欟欸欷盜欹飮歇歃歉歐歙歔歛歟歡歸歹歿殀殄殃殍殘殕殞殤殪殫殯殲殱殳殷殼毆毋毓毟毬毫毳毯麾氈氓气氛氤氣汞汕汢汪沂沍沚沁沛汾汨汳沒沐泄泱泓沽泗泅泝沮沱沾沺泛泯泙泪洟衍洶洫洽洸洙洵洳洒洌浣涓浤浚浹浙涎涕濤涅淹渕渊涵淇淦涸淆淬淞淌淨淒淅淺淙淤淕淪淮渭湮渮渙湲湟渾渣湫渫湶湍渟湃渺湎渤滿渝游溂溪溘滉溷滓溽溯滄溲滔滕溏溥滂溟潁漑灌滬滸滾漿滲漱滯漲滌漾漓滷澆潺潸澁澀潯潛濳潭澂潼潘澎澑濂潦澳澣澡澤澹濆澪濟濕濬濔濘濱濮濛瀉瀋濺瀑瀁瀏濾瀛瀚潴瀝瀘瀟瀰瀾瀲灑灣炙炒炯烱炬炸炳炮烟烋烝烙焉烽焜焙煥煕熈煦煢煌煖煬熏燻熄熕熨熬燗熹熾燒燉燔燎燠燬燧燵燼燹燿爍爐爛爨爭爬爰爲爻爼爿牀牆牋牘牴牾犂犁犇犒犖犢犧犹犲狃狆狄狎狒狢狠狡狹狷倏猗猊猜猖猝猴猯猩猥猾獎獏默獗獪獨獰獸獵獻獺珈玳珎玻珀珥珮珞璢琅瑯琥珸琲琺瑕琿瑟瑙瑁瑜瑩瑰瑣瑪瑶瑾璋璞璧瓊瓏瓔珱瓠瓣瓧瓩瓮瓲瓰瓱瓸瓷甄甃甅甌甎甍甕甓甞甦甬甼畄畍畊畉畛畆畚畩畤畧畫畭畸當疆疇畴疊疉疂疔疚疝疥疣痂疳痃疵疽疸疼疱痍痊痒痙痣痞痾痿痼瘁痰痺痲痳瘋瘍瘉瘟瘧瘠瘡瘢瘤瘴瘰瘻癇癈癆癜癘癡癢癨癩癪癧癬癰癲癶癸發皀皃皈皋皎皖皓皙皚皰皴皸皹皺盂盍盖盒盞盡盥盧盪蘯盻眈眇眄眩眤眞眥眦眛眷眸睇睚睨睫睛睥睿睾睹瞎瞋瞑瞠瞞瞰瞶瞹瞿瞼瞽瞻矇矍矗矚矜矣矮矼砌砒礦砠礪硅碎硴碆硼碚碌碣碵碪碯磑磆磋磔碾碼磅磊磬磧磚磽磴礇礒礑礙礬礫祀祠祗祟祚祕祓祺祿禊禝禧齋禪禮禳禹禺秉秕秧秬秡秣稈稍稘稙稠稟禀稱稻稾稷穃穗穉穡穢穩龝穰穹穽窈窗窕窘窖窩竈窰窶竅竄窿邃竇竊竍竏竕竓站竚竝竡竢竦竭竰笂笏笊笆笳笘笙笞笵笨笶筐筺笄筍笋筌筅筵筥筴筧筰筱筬筮箝箘箟箍箜箚箋箒箏筝箙篋篁篌篏箴篆篝篩簑簔篦篥籠簀簇簓篳篷簗簍篶簣簧簪簟簷簫簽籌籃籔籏籀籐籘籟籤籖籥籬籵粃粐粤粭粢粫粡粨粳粲粱粮粹粽糀糅糂糘糒糜糢鬻糯糲糴糶糺紆紂紜紕紊絅絋紮紲紿紵絆絳絖絎絲絨絮絏絣經綉絛綏絽綛綺綮綣綵緇綽綫總綢綯緜綸綟綰緘緝緤緞緻緲緡縅縊縣縡縒縱縟縉縋縢繆繦縻縵縹繃縷縲縺繧繝繖繞繙繚繹繪繩繼繻纃緕繽辮繿纈纉續纒纐纓纔纖纎纛纜缸缺罅罌罍罎罐网罕罔罘罟罠罨罩罧罸羂羆羃羈羇羌羔羞羝羚羣羯羲羹羮羶羸譱翅翆翊翕翔翡翦翩翳翹飜耆耄耋耒耘耙耜耡耨耿耻聊聆聒聘聚聟聢聨聳聲聰聶聹聽聿肄肆肅肛肓肚肭冐肬胛胥胙胝胄胚胖脉胯胱脛脩脣脯腋隋腆脾腓腑胼腱腮腥腦腴膃膈膊膀膂膠膕膤膣腟膓膩膰膵膾膸膽臀臂膺臉臍臑臙臘臈臚臟臠臧臺臻臾舁舂舅與舊舍舐舖舩舫舸舳艀艙艘艝艚艟艤艢艨艪艫舮艱艷艸艾芍芒芫芟芻芬苡苣苟苒苴苳苺莓范苻苹苞茆苜茉苙茵茴茖茲茱荀茹荐荅茯茫茗茘莅莚莪莟莢莖茣莎莇莊荼莵荳荵莠莉莨菴萓菫菎菽萃菘萋菁菷萇菠菲萍萢萠莽萸蔆菻葭萪萼蕚蒄葷葫蒭葮蒂葩葆萬葯葹萵蓊葢蒹蒿蒟蓙蓍蒻蓚蓐蓁蓆蓖蒡蔡蓿蓴蔗蔘蔬蔟蔕蔔蓼蕀蕣蕘蕈蕁蘂蕋蕕薀薤薈薑薊薨蕭薔薛藪薇薜蕷蕾薐藉薺藏薹藐藕藝藥藜藹蘊蘓蘋藾藺蘆蘢蘚蘰蘿虍乕虔號虧虱蚓蚣蚩蚪蚋蚌蚶蚯蛄蛆蚰蛉蠣蚫蛔蛞蛩蛬蛟蛛蛯蜒蜆蜈蜀蜃蛻蜑蜉蜍蛹蜊蜴蜿蜷蜻蜥蜩蜚蝠蝟蝸蝌蝎蝴蝗蝨蝮蝙蝓蝣蝪蠅螢螟螂螯蟋螽蟀蟐雖螫蟄螳蟇蟆螻蟯蟲蟠蠏蠍蟾蟶蟷蠎蟒蠑蠖蠕蠢蠡蠱蠶蠹蠧蠻衄衂衒衙衞衢衫袁衾袞衵衽袵衲袂袗袒袮袙袢袍袤袰袿袱裃裄裔裘裙裝裹褂裼裴裨裲褄褌褊褓襃褞褥褪褫襁襄褻褶褸襌褝襠襞襦襤襭襪襯襴襷襾覃覈覊覓覘覡覩覦覬覯覲覺覽覿觀觚觜觝觧觴觸訃訖訐訌訛訝訥訶詁詛詒詆詈詼詭詬詢誅誂誄誨誡誑誥誦誚誣諄諍諂諚諫諳諧諤諱謔諠諢諷諞諛謌謇謚諡謖謐謗謠謳鞫謦謫謾謨譁譌譏譎證譖譛譚譫譟譬譯譴譽讀讌讎讒讓讖讙讚谺豁谿豈豌豎豐豕豢豬豸豺貂貉貅貊貍貎貔豼貘戝貭貪貽貲貳貮貶賈賁賤賣賚賽賺賻贄贅贊贇贏贍贐齎贓賍贔贖赧赭赱赳趁趙跂趾趺跏跚跖跌跛跋跪跫跟跣跼踈踉跿踝踞踐踟蹂踵踰踴蹊蹇蹉蹌蹐蹈蹙蹤蹠踪蹣蹕蹶蹲蹼躁躇躅躄躋躊躓躑躔躙躪躡躬躰軆躱躾軅軈軋軛軣軼軻軫軾輊輅輕輒輙輓輜輟輛輌輦輳輻輹轅轂輾轌轉轆轎轗轜轢轣轤辜辟辣辭辯辷迚迥迢迪迯邇迴逅迹迺逑逕逡逍逞逖逋逧逶逵逹迸遏遐遑遒逎遉逾遖遘遞遨遯遶隨遲邂遽邁邀邊邉邏邨邯邱邵郢郤扈郛鄂鄒鄙鄲鄰酊酖酘酣酥酩酳酲醋醉醂醢醫醯醪醵醴醺釀釁釉釋釐釖釟釡釛釼釵釶鈞釿鈔鈬鈕鈑鉞鉗鉅鉉鉤鉈銕鈿鉋鉐銜銖銓銛鉚鋏銹銷鋩錏鋺鍄錮錙錢錚錣錺錵錻鍜鍠鍼鍮鍖鎰鎬鎭鎔鎹鏖鏗鏨鏥鏘鏃鏝鏐鏈鏤鐚鐔鐓鐃鐇鐐鐶鐫鐵鐡鐺鑁鑒鑄鑛鑠鑢鑞鑪鈩鑰鑵鑷鑽鑚鑼鑾钁鑿閂閇閊閔閖閘閙閠閨閧閭閼閻閹閾闊濶闃闍闌闕闔闖關闡闥闢阡阨阮阯陂陌陏陋陷陜陞陝陟陦陲陬隍隘隕隗險隧隱隲隰隴隶隸隹雎雋雉雍襍雜霍雕雹霄霆霈霓霎霑霏霖霙霤霪霰霹霽霾靄靆靈靂靉靜靠靤靦靨勒靫靱靹鞅靼鞁靺鞆鞋鞏鞐鞜鞨鞦鞣鞳鞴韃韆韈韋韜韭齏韲竟韶韵頏頌頸頤頡頷頽顆顏顋顫顯顰顱顴顳颪颯颱颶飄飃飆飩飫餃餉餒餔餘餡餝餞餤餠餬餮餽餾饂饉饅饐饋饑饒饌饕馗馘馥馭馮馼駟駛駝駘駑駭駮駱駲駻駸騁騏騅駢騙騫騷驅驂驀驃騾驕驍驛驗驟驢驥驤驩驫驪骭骰骼髀髏髑髓體髞髟髢髣髦髯髫髮髴髱髷髻鬆鬘鬚鬟鬢鬣鬥鬧鬨鬩鬪鬮鬯鬲魄魃魏魍魎魑魘魴鮓鮃鮑鮖鮗鮟鮠鮨鮴鯀鯊鮹鯆鯏鯑鯒鯣鯢鯤鯔鯡鰺鯲鯱鯰鰕鰔鰉鰓鰌鰆鰈鰒鰊鰄鰮鰛鰥鰤鰡鰰鱇鰲鱆鰾鱚鱠鱧鱶鱸鳧鳬鳰鴉鴈鳫鴃鴆鴪鴦鶯鴣鴟鵄鴕鴒鵁鴿鴾鵆鵈鵝鵞鵤鵑鵐鵙鵲鶉鶇鶫鵯鵺鶚鶤鶩鶲鷄鷁鶻鶸鶺鷆鷏鷂鷙鷓鷸鷦鷭鷯鷽鸚鸛鸞鹵鹹鹽麁麈麋麌麒麕麑麝麥麩麸麪麭靡黌黎黏黐黔黜點黝黠黥黨黯黴黶黷黹黻黼黽鼇鼈皷鼕鼡鼬鼾齊齒齔齣齟齠齡齦齧齬齪齷齲齶龕龜龠堯槇遙瑤凜熙纊褜鍈銈蓜俉炻昱棈鋹曻彅丨仡仼伀伃伹佖侒侊侚侔俍偀倢俿倞偆偰偂傔僴僘兊兤冝冾凬刕劜劦勀勛匀匇匤卲厓厲叝﨎咜咊咩哿喆坙坥垬埈埇﨏塚增墲夋奓奛奝奣妤妺孖寀甯寘寬尞岦岺峵崧嵓﨑嵂嵭嶸嶹巐弡弴彧德忞恝悅悊惞惕愠惲愑愷愰憘戓抦揵摠撝擎敎昀昕昻昉昮昞昤晥晗晙晴晳暙暠暲暿曺朎朗杦枻桒柀栁桄棏﨓楨﨔榘槢樰橫橆橳橾櫢櫤毖氿汜沆汯泚洄涇浯涖涬淏淸淲淼渹湜渧渼溿澈澵濵瀅瀇瀨炅炫焏焄煜煆煇凞燁燾犱犾猤猪獷玽珉珖珣珒琇珵琦琪琩琮瑢璉璟甁畯皂皜皞皛皦益睆劯砡硎硤硺礰礼神祥禔福禛竑竧靖竫箞精絈絜綷綠緖繒罇羡羽茁荢荿菇菶葈蒴蕓蕙蕫﨟薰蘒﨡蠇裵訒訷詹誧誾諟諸諶譓譿賰賴贒赶﨣軏﨤逸遧郞都鄕鄧釚釗釞釭釮釤釥鈆鈐鈊鈺鉀鈼鉎鉙鉑鈹鉧銧鉷鉸鋧鋗鋙鋐﨧鋕鋠鋓錥錡鋻﨨錞鋿錝錂鍰鍗鎤鏆鏞鏸鐱鑅鑈閒隆﨩隝隯霳霻靃靍靏靑靕顗顥飯飼餧館馞驎髙髜魵魲鮏鮱鮻鰀鵰鵫鶴鸙黑ⅰⅱⅲⅳⅴⅵⅶⅷⅸⅹⅰⅱⅲⅳⅴⅵⅶⅷⅸⅹⅠⅡⅢⅣⅤⅥⅦⅧⅨⅩ￢￤＇＂㈱№℡∵纊褜鍈銈蓜俉炻昱棈鋹曻彅丨仡仼伀伃伹佖侒侊侚侔俍偀倢俿倞偆偰偂傔僴僘兊兤冝冾凬刕劜劦勀勛匀匇匤卲厓厲叝﨎咜咊咩哿喆坙坥垬埈埇﨏塚增墲夋奓奛奝奣妤妺孖寀甯寘寬尞岦岺峵崧嵓﨑嵂嵭嶸嶹巐弡弴彧德忞恝悅悊惞惕愠惲愑愷愰憘戓抦揵摠撝擎敎昀昕昻昉昮昞昤晥晗晙晴晳暙暠暲暿曺朎朗杦枻桒柀栁桄棏﨓楨﨔榘槢樰橫橆橳橾櫢櫤毖氿汜沆汯泚洄涇浯涖涬淏淸淲淼渹湜渧渼溿澈澵濵瀅瀇瀨炅炫焏焄煜煆煇凞燁燾犱犾猤猪獷玽珉珖珣珒琇珵琦琪琩琮瑢璉璟甁畯皂皜皞皛皦益睆劯砡硎硤硺礰礼神祥禔福禛竑竧靖竫箞精絈絜綷綠緖繒罇羡羽茁荢荿菇菶葈蒴蕓蕙蕫﨟薰蘒﨡蠇裵訒訷詹誧誾諟諸諶譓譿賰賴贒赶﨣軏﨤逸遧郞都鄕鄧釚釗釞釭釮釤釥鈆鈐鈊鈺鉀鈼鉎鉙鉑鈹鉧銧鉷鉸鋧鋗鋙鋐﨧鋕鋠鋓錥錡鋻﨨錞鋿錝錂鍰鍗鎤鏆鏞鏸鐱鑅鑈閒隆﨩隝隯霳霻靃靍靏靑靕顗顥飯飼餧館馞驎髙髜魵魲鮏鮱鮻鰀鵰鵫鶴鸙黑ー

Korean
range:ᄀ-ᇿ㄰-㆏ꥠ-꥿ힰ-퟿가-힣